[{"value": {"id": 1738680, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total number of staff employed to review Personal Independence Payment claims is; and how many fraudulent claims were made in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "DWP currently has 2,700 FTE employed to review Personal Independence Payment Claims. Staff RoleFTEDS PIP New Claims and Award Reviews2700 Notes:Data is correct as of 04th November 2024.Data for PIP New Claims and Award Reviews staff has been derived from ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738714, "askingMemberId": 5267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of (a) the number of constituents in Earley and Woodley who will be impacted by the proposed reforms to the Work Capability Assessment and (b) the average financial impact on ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department does not hold constituency-level information about the specific Work Capability Assessment descriptors met by claimants, so we are unable to estimate impacts for individual constituencies robustly.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Work Capability Assessment: Earley and Woodley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738723, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding that will be allocated to NHS services in Essex in each of the nex", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The recent Budget set out the overall funding for the Department for 2024/25 and 2025/26. In terms of the next five years, the funding that will be allocated to the three integrated care boards covering Essex will be set out alongside planning guidance fo...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Essex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738685, "askingMemberId": 4617, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the Trade Remedies Authority\u2019s recent recommendation to remove anti-dumping measures on e-bikes from China and the potential imp", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["12285"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK applies separate anti-dumping and anti-subsidy measures on imports of Chinese e-bikes. The Trade Remedies Authority is currently conducting transition reviews of both measures and I therefore cannot comment further. Relevant information will be pub...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Bicycles: Antidumping Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12285", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738683, "askingMemberId": 4617, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Trade Remedies Authority's recommendation to remove anti-dumping measures on e-bikes on the UK Cycle Manufacturing Industry.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["12287"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 632, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK applies separate anti-dumping and anti-subsidy measures on imports of Chinese e-bikes. The Trade Remedies Authority is currently conducting transition reviews of both measures and I therefore cannot comment further. Relevant information will be pub...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Bicycles: Antidumping Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12287", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738697, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12290", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of the alcohol duty freeze on pubs in South Shropshire.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Pubs and breweries make an enormous contribution to our economy and society, and this is recognised in the tax system. At the Budget, the Chancellor cut alcohol duty on qualifying draught products \u2013 approximately 60% of the alcoholic drinks sold in pubs. ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholic Drinks: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738689, "askingMemberId": 3912, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with the Charity Commission on when the Commission plans to provide a substantive reply to the letter from the Conservative Party to the Commission of 14 June 2024, a", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4607, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Charity Commission responded to the Conservative Party\u2019s Legal Officer on 15th August 2024, providing a full update on the case in question. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Charity Commission: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739378, "askingMemberId": 5267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, how many people claim benefits that were uprated at the Budget in (a) Earley and Woodley constituency, (b) each region and", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The estimated number of individuals in families benefitting from the uprating of benefits in the financial year 2025/26 in each region of the UK and the UK overall can be found here Benefit uprating: estimated number and type of families and individuals i...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739266, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) regulate and (b) monitor (i) MBR Acres and (ii) other breeding facilities to ensure compliance with animal welfare standards.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4243, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 (ASPA) provides protections for animals bred in the UK for use in scientific procedures. All establishments licenced to breed protected animals under ASPA are required to comply with the published Code of Pract...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Breeding: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739191, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12388", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 10967 on Government Departments: Disclosure of Information, if he will outline (a) potential changes to the scope, manner and frequency of Ministerial report", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government will introduce a register for ministers\u2019 gifts and hospitality bringing publication of ministerial transparency data on a broadly equivalent basis to the parliamentary register.This Government is fully committed to transparency and opennes...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738710, "askingMemberId": 5267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of (a) the number of constituents in Earley and Woodley who will be affected by reductions in sickness benefits announced at the budget and (b) the average financial impact of", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "No reductions in sickness benefits were announced at the Budget.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sickness Benefits: Earley and Woodley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738729, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce ambulance waiting times in the South West.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government has committed to supporting the National Health Service to improve performance and achieve the standards set out in the NHS Constitution, including for ambulance response times.As a first step, my Rt Hon. Friend, the Secretary of State for ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ambulance Services: South West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739222, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress she has made on supporting pothole repairs in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government takes the condition of local roads very seriously and is committed to maintaining and renewing the local highway network.At Budget 2024, the Chancellor announced an extra \u00a3500 million for local highway maintenance for the 2025/26 financial ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: South Holland and the Deepings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739299, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help reduce congestion on roads in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": " This Government is committed to maintaining and renewing our road network so it can serve all road users and is safe. Traffic management of local roads is the responsibility of local traffic authorities who are best placed to understand local circumstanc...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Traffic: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739345, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road accidents there were in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire in the most recent period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Data on road injury collisions are reported by police using the STATS19 system. The number of personal injury road collisions reported to police in each of the areas requested in 2023 are shown in the table below.AreaAll collisionsSouth Holland and the De...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: South Holland and the Deepings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739274, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will make an estimate of the cost of closing roads during flooding in (a) Bedfordshire and (b) nationally in September.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department recognises the profound importance of our country\u2019s road network in moving people, goods, and services around the country. The economic impact of closing roads will vary greatly depending on the roads in question and on the scale and severi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Floods", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739431, "askingMemberId": 5349, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the condition of local roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government takes the condition of local roads very seriously and is committed to maintaining and renewing the local highway network. It publishes data annually on the condition of local roads which is available on gov.uk.At Budget 2024, the Chancellor...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738702, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the (a) value and (b) volume of coal imported into the UK was in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4998, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Data showing the value and volume of coal imported into the UK is presented in the following table: 20192020202120222023UK coal imports (million tonnes)5.43.74.56.62.9Value of UK coal imports (\u00a3m)5743184701,573519Source: HMRC trade data     ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coal: Imports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738741, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will place sanctions on the (a) Montenegro based company International Business Corporation Bar and (b) Serbia based company Ventrade DOO for supplying Russia with adva", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4264, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK remains steadfast in our support to Ukraine. Together with our international partners, we have implemented the most severe package of sanctions ever imposed on a major economy. The UK alone has sanctioned more than 2,000 individuals and entities un...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Sanctions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738667, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of proposals to require all rented homes to reach an EPC C standard by 2030 on the level of social housebuilding.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12281", "12282"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the Housing Minister's answer to Question UIN 11383 on 31 October 2024, he set out the measures the Government is taking to deliver the biggest increase in social and affordable housebuilding in a generation.The Government is committed to working with ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Energy Performance Certificates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12281", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12282", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738666, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) section 42 of the Social Housing (Regulation) Act 2023 and (b) fire safety regulations introduced since the Grenfell T", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12281", "12283"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the Housing Minister's answer to Question UIN 11383 on 31 October 2024, he set out the measures the Government is taking to deliver the biggest increase in social and affordable housebuilding in a generation.The Government is committed to working with ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12281", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12283", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738665, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) section 42 of the Social Housing (Regulation) Act 2023 and (b) fire safety regulations introduced since the Grenfell T", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12282", "12283"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "In the Housing Minister's answer to Question UIN 11383 on 31 October 2024, he set out the measures the Government is taking to deliver the biggest increase in social and affordable housebuilding in a generation.The Government is committed to working with ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arms Length Management Organisations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12282", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12283", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738668, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to ensure that the building safety regulator is sufficiently resourced to adequately perform its functions.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "MHCLG remain committed to ensuring the BSR are properly funded to deliver the most significant changes to building safety for generations. The BSR\u2019s mission is to protect people and places, stewarding a built environment where buildings are long-lasting a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Building Safety Regulator", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738670, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 October 2024 to Question 5620 on Schools: Buildings, what stage of the School Rebuilding Programme are (a) Green Meadow Primary School and (b) King Edward VI Balaam Wood Academy in B", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4653, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Green Meadow Primary School is in group 2 of the School Rebuilding Programme. Projects in group 2 are expected to commence with planning and feasibility work from April 2025.King Edward VI Balaam Wood Academy is in group 3 and is currently expected to com...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "School Rebuilding Programme: Birmingham Northfield", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738731, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12341", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil service staff earned above \u00a3100,000 a year in (a) January 2024 and (b) the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["11723"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5305, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Civil Service Statistics (Table 35) provides information on the number of civil servants earning over \u00a3100,000 and in other bandings. The latest information can be found here: https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/civil-service-statistics-2024 The prev...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Senior Civil Servants: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "11723", "dateTabled": "2024-10-29T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738658, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12247", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Oral Statement of 30 October 2024 on Financial Statement and Budget Report, Official Report, column 819, what the evidential basis is for the estimate that 75% of family farms will not be affec", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government has published information about reforms to agricultural property relief at: https://www.gov.uk/government/news/what-are-the-changes-to-agricultural-property-relief. Almost three-quarters of estates claiming agricultural property relief (or ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738707, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12294", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of the increase to employer's national insurance contributions on the Ministry of Def", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4797, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government will be supporting departments with the cost of additional employer national insurance contributions. This is in line with the Government\u2019s usual approach to supporting the public sector, as was the case with the previous government\u2019s Healt...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Ministry of Defence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738700, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department plans to appeal the Dillon judgement handed down in the Belfast Court of Appeal on 20 September 2024, NICA 59.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 413, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is committed to repealing and replacing the Legacy Act, and to implementing legacy mechanisms that are compliant with human rights and can be supported by communities across Northern Ireland. We are considering the implications of the Court...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Northern Ireland Troubles (Legacy and Reconciliation) Act 2023", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738669, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much additional security funding the Government plans to provide to the Police Service of Northern Ireland in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 413, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Recognising the unique security situation in Northern Ireland, the UK Government makes an additional contribution to the PSNI through Additional Security Funding.As we announced in the Spending Review last week we have increased Additional Security Fundin...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police Service of Northern Ireland: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739365, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12416", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 15 January 2024 to Question 7805 on Ministers: Members' Interests, what the budget is for the development of the single platform for transparency data; and which organisation has ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government is committed to looking at how the range of information published can be improved and made as useful as possible.This Government will introduce a register for ministers\u2019 gifts and hospitality bringing publication of ministerial transparenc...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739359, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12412", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to table 5 of the National Security and Investment Act 2021: Annual Report 2023-24, published on 10 September 2024, for what reason each of the withdrawals from a called in acquisition withdrew; a", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "There is no requirement for parties to inform the Government before they withdraw from acquisitions or to tell the Government the reasons behind the withdrawal.Parties might withdraw from deals for a variety of reasons, including reasons unrelated to the ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK: National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738715, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Government Hospitality wine cellar biennial report 2022 to 2024, published on 31 October 2024, for what occasion was a half bottle of 1948 Frapin Grande", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["12257"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The cognac and wine referred to formed part of the Government Wine Committee's tasting. The Committee, which convenes three times a year, provides advice on the management of the Government Wine Cellar.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Hospitality: Spirits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12257", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738713, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Government Hospitality wine cellar biennial report 2022 to 2024, published on 31 October 2024, for what occasions were two bottles of 1989 Batard-Montra", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12258"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The cognac and wine referred to formed part of the Government Wine Committee's tasting. The Committee, which convenes three times a year, provides advice on the management of the Government Wine Cellar.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Hospitality: Wines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12258", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738712, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Government Hospitality wine cellar biennial report 2022 to 2024, published on 31 October 2024, for what occasions were three bottles of 1931 Quinta do N", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12253", "12254", "12255"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The cognac, wine, and port referenced were consumed at a Minister-led event to mark the centenary of the Government Wine Cellar in December 2023.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Hospitality: Wines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12253", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12254", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12255", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738711, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Government Hospitality wine cellar biennial report 2022 to 2024, published on 31 October 2024, for what occasions were four bottles of 1983 Chateau Marg", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12253", "12254", "12256"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The cognac, wine, and port referenced were consumed at a Minister-led event to mark the centenary of the Government Wine Cellar in December 2023.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Hospitality: Wines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12253", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12254", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12256", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738709, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Government Hospitality wine cellar biennial report 2022 to 2024, published on 31 October 2024, for what occasions were six bottles of 1988 Echezeaux Dom", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12253", "12255", "12256"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The cognac, wine, and port referenced were consumed at a Minister-led event to mark the centenary of the Government Wine Cellar in December 2023.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Hospitality: Wines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12253", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12255", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12256", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738708, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Government Hospitality wine cellar biennial report 2022 to 2024, published on 31 October 2024, for what occasion was a bottle of 1922 Hine Cognac consum", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["12254", "12255", "12256"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4523, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The cognac, wine, and port referenced were consumed at a Minister-led event to mark the centenary of the Government Wine Cellar in December 2023.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Hospitality: Spirits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "12254", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12255", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "12256", "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738699, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve the enforcement of animal welfare penalty notices.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Enforcement authorities have been able to issue penalty notices for a range of animal health and welfare offences since 1 January 2024. At the end of each financial year, enforcement authorities are required to submit an annual report to Defra on how many...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Welfare: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738664, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to take steps to increase the amount of freight transported by rail.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government recognises that the economic and environmental potential of rail freight is significant and is committed to supporting its growth.There will be a statutory duty on Great British Railways to promote the use of rail freight and there will be ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738733, "askingMemberId": 4617, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the informed choice framework for prostate cancer screening.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Screening for prostate cancer is currently not recommended by the UK National Screening Committees. This is because of the inaccuracy of the current best test called Prostate Specific Antigen (PSA).The Prostate Cancer Risk Management Programme provides ge...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738722, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding he plans to allocate to public health grants for local authorities in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "We will confirm 2025/26 public health grant allocations later this year, and will confirm future years\u2019 allocations following the upcoming Spending Review in Spring 2025.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Health: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738734, "askingMemberId": 4617, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of potential disparities in access to prostate cancer screening among men of different (a) races and (b) socio-economic statuses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1506, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Screening for prostate cancer is currently not recommended by the UK National Screening Committees (UK NSC). This is because of the inaccuracy of the current best test, called Prostate Specific Antigen (PSA).The UK NSC is carrying out an evidence review o...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738753, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) funding and (b) other support his Department is providing to farmers to transition to more sustainable agricultural practices in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4382, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra\u2019s farming budget will be \u00a32.4 billion in 2025/26. This will include the largest ever budget directed at sustainable food production and nature\u2019s recovery in our country\u2019s history: \u00a31.8 billion for environmental land management schemes. This funding ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: West Dorset", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738673, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12261", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled National Security and Investment Act 2021: Annual Report 2023-24, published on 10 September 2024, for what reason there was the reduction in the average ti", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The time taken to issue a final order for each called in acquisition will depend on the facts of the case. Given the small number of final orders (five) issued in this reporting period (1 April 2023 to 31 March 2024), no conclusions should be drawn about ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK: National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740279, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-14T00:00:00", "uin": "901149", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the number of farms that will be affected by changes to agricultural property relief and business property relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740226, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he had with his Chinese counterpart on trade deals during his visit to China in October 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740276, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Patient Safety Commissioner's report entitled The Hughes Report: Options for redress for those harmed by valproate and pelvic mesh, published on 7 February 2024, what assessme", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740275, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential risk to vulnerable people of the accidental ingestion of hearing aid batteries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740274, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to improve the (a) diagnosis and (b) treatment of Lyme disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740273, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the yearly cost to the NHS is of the provision of replacement hearing aid batteries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740272, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on the provision of rechargable hearing aids on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740271, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2024 to Question 8363, what minimum requirements his Department set out as being an expectation in any legitimate interest access\u00a0regime\u00a0", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740270, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13152", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) promoters and (b) operators of schemes now subject to the Loan Charge have been prosecuted.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740269, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, Education what steps her Department is taking to ensure Ofsted inspections assess the steps schools take to ensure children\u2019s wellbeing on the school estate.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740268, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the metrics by which the new Ofsted report cards will judge their inclusion criterion.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740267, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of ensuring that the Curriculum and Assessment Review focuses on the provision of (a) inclusive and (b) nurturing approaches to education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740266, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2024 to Question 9826 on Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in his Departmen", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740265, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help improve outcomes for bowel cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740264, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13146", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2024 to Question 9603 on Attorney General: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in her Department's headquarters in London; and how many individual desks are available i", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740263, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2024, to Question 9286, on Civil Servants, how many civil servants are assigned to work in her Department's headquarters in London; and how many individual desks are", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740262, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2024 to Question 9611 on Ministry of Defence: Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in his Department\u2019s HQ office in the most recent four weeks for which figures ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740261, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9268 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service (HMCTS): Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in HMCTS\u2019s main office; and how many individual desks", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740260, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9268 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service (HMCTS): Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in HMCTS\u2019s main office in the most recent four weeks for w", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740259, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9266 on Ministry of Justice: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in her Department's headquarters in London; and how many individual desks", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740258, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9266 on Ministry of Justice: Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in her Department\u2019s headquarters office in the most recent four weeks for whic", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740257, "askingMemberId": 5123, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-18T00:00:00", "uin": "13139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he plans to publish new guidance on Community Benefits for Electricity Transmission Network Infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740256, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the impact of increasing employers' national insurance contributions on businesses in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740255, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to support family-owned farms with rising business costs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740254, "askingMemberId": 5221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13136", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of removing Value Added Tax from automated external defibrillators.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740253, "askingMemberId": 5241, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure local authorities implement the recommendations of the Cass review in schools they oversee.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740252, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the economic contribution of farming to (a) Derbyshire and (b) South Derbyshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740251, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will meet the hon. Member for South Basildon and East Thurrock to discuss pylons.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740250, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he plans to take steps to strengthen bilateral cooperation with Australia on matters relating to the (a) sports and (b) cultural sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740249, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential use of Artificial Intelligence in the health sector to improve patient outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740248, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the availability of changing and bathroom facilities for women at grassroots sporting venues.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740247, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans he has to support Afghan women (a) in Afghanistan and (b) living as refugees (i) in the UK and (ii) around the world.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740246, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had recent discussions with her French counterpart on preventing small boats from crossing the Channel by intercepting them mid-journey.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740245, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure value for money in (a) medicines and (b) medical supplies in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740244, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will facilitate the issuing of visas to (a) Gazan and (b) other academics whose supporting paperwork has been lost during the conflict in the Middle East.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740243, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase digital learning opportunities across (a) schools and (b) colleges.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740242, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will take steps with Cabinet colleagues to support the work of the Council for At-Risk Academics.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740241, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has had recent discussions with his US counterpart on a free trade agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740240, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase manufacturing jobs in (a) Essex and (b) nationally.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740239, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding her Department has provided for the repair of potholes (a) in Great Yarmouth constituency and (b) nationally in each of the last ten years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740238, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote awareness of the (a) Commonwealth of Nations, (b) Monarchy and (c) Commonwealth realms in (i) schools in England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740237, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing additional support to (a) GP pra", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740236, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13118", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding the Government allocated to spend on advertising in each year since 2015, broken down by Department.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740235, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13117", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding the Government has allocated for spending on advertising (a) in total and (b) by Department over the next Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740234, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to encourage Great British Energy to consult with local communities on the development of renewable energy projects.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740233, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average length of time was for planning permission to be granted for (a) businesses and (b) residential properties in (i) Great Yarmouth constituency and (ii) England in", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740232, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the capacity of state schools to accommodate a potential increase in students transferring from private schools; and whether students transferring from private schools in rural a", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740231, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the expiration of the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement provisions on fishing on 30 June 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740230, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13112", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to publish the 2025 edition of the National Risk Register; and whether she plans to enable Parliament to (a) feed into and (b) scrutinise that register.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740229, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure compliance with the Accessible Information Standard across the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740228, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13110", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the number of (a) Suspicious Activity Reports and (b) Defence Against Money Laundering Suspicious Activity Reports from electronic pay", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740227, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) limiting and (b) banning commercial trading of fishing licence quotas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740156, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13108", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many electronic money institutions have (a) had their activities restricted and (b) been de-authorised following an investigation by the Financial Conduct Authority.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740155, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing (a) provenance and (b) tax tests to prevent vessels with foreign owners from flying a UK flag of convenience when c", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740154, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of banning all foreign supertrawlers from UK waters.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740153, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing legislation to require that all fish caught in (a) UK territorial waters and (b) the UK exclusive economic zone are", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740152, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of compliance with the Accessible Information Standard in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740151, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to implement section 95 of the Health and Care Act 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740150, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will (a) introduce a licence fee for access to UK (a) territorial and (b) exclusive economic zone waters to foreign vessels granted permission to catch fish and (b) use that fee ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740149, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if the Prime Minister will have discussions with the Royal Household on issuing an invitation for a state visit to President-Elect Trump.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740148, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will amend the Merchant Shipping Act 1995 in line with the Merchant Shipping Act 1988.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740147, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to reduce waiting times for driving tests in (a) rural areas and (b) urban areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740146, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he plans to launch the consultation on technical issues for the renewable liquid heating fuel obligation under Section 159 of the Energy Act 2023; and what steps he is taking to support ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740145, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13097", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the revenue raised by the ten percent tariff imposed on the import of mobility scooters.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740143, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13096", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will increase the number of banking hubs due to be built in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740142, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13095", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases of mis-sold Equity Release schemes have been referred to the Financial Ombudsmen in the last two years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740141, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will expand the list of prescribed people for whistleblowing to include (a) job applicants, (b) trustees, (c) independent contractors and (d) trade union representatives.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740140, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what his planned timetable is for the review of the whistleblowing framework.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740139, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13092", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to increase the number of banking hubs in rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740138, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13091", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what progress she has made on plans to create a whistleblowing incentive program within the Serious Fraud Office.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740136, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of voters are registered to vote by post in each parliamentary constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740135, "askingMemberId": 5298, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-18T00:00:00", "uin": "13089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what progress he has made on establishing the Office for Clean Energy Jobs; and when he plans to publish its terms of reference.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740134, "askingMemberId": 5109, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on (a) renewing the national maternity safety ambitions beyond 2025 and (b) amending those ambitions to include reducing inequalities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740133, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data his Department holds on the average class size at (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Great Yarmouth constituency and (ii) England in each of the last twenty years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740132, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many dentists have closed in (a) Great Yarmouth constituency and (b) Norfolk since 2016.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740131, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of trends in the level of funding in his Department's statistics entitled Adult Social Care Activity and Finance Report, E", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740129, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of opening a jobcentre in St Neots.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740128, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of opening a driving test centre in St Neots.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740127, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to uprate the state pension for British pensioners residing overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740126, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support British pensioners residing overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740123, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13080", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to (a) agricultural property relief and (b) business property relief on the finances of farms of 215 acres in size.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740116, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the priorities of (a) children and (b) young people with cancer are included within the ten-year plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740114, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve (a) diagnosis and (b) referral rates for 13\u201324-year-olds with cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740112, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on the NHS Long Term plan target of increasing clinical trial participation for children and young people with cancer to 50% by 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740111, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many yellow card reports there have been on Covid-19 vaccines.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740106, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve uptake of community alcohol services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740105, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for mental health diagnoses of children.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740104, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to tackle (a) mental health and (b) suicide rates among mothers in the twelve months postpartum.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740103, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) GPs and (b) other healthcare professionals receive adequate training to (a) screen for bipolar disorder, (b) manage it effectively and (c) prevent the ina", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740101, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to create specialist services for people with bipolar disorder.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740097, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to introduce Bikeability training to the national curriculum.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740085, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what charges were issued to non-UK residents of what nationalities not entitled to free secondary healthcare by the James Paget NHS trust for each treatment in each of the last three financial year", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740084, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the potential implications for her policies of case backlogs in (a) criminal and (b) civil courts.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740083, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure people without Maths and English GCSEs can access appropriate apprenticeship schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740082, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure blood specimens taken for prostate specific antigen tests are separated within 16 hours.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740081, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of blood specimens taken for prostate specific antigen tests are separated within 16 hours.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740080, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle violence against women and girls in North Warwickshire and Bedworth constituency; and if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the rate of prosec", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740079, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to mitigate (a) noise, (b) dust and (c) traffic disruption relating to HS2 works.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740078, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13062", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many high-street branches of (a) banks and (b) building societies have closed in North Warwickshire and Bedworth constituency since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740077, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has commissioned research on the potential impact of financial skills training on the ability of young people to manage their finances; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740076, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many small and medium-sized businesses in North Warwickshire and Bedworth constituency closed between 2010 and 2024; and what steps he is taking to ensure small and medium sized businesses in North", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740075, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship schemes are operating in (a) North Warwickshire and Bedworth constituency, (b) North Warwickshire and (c) Nuneaton and Bedworth.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740074, "askingMemberId": 5328, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will list every case in which Secretaries of State have granted consent under Section 128(1) of the 1972 Local Government Act for disposal of building for (a) less than be", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740073, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support British pensioners residing overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740072, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13056", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the press notice entitled Prime Minister unveils game changing investment to tackle national security threat from people smuggling gangs, published on 4 November 2024, whether the \u00a375m funding anno", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740070, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the (a) quality and (b) total area coverage area for (i) 5G and (ii) other wireless data reception in (A) Wokingham and (B) along intercity transport rout", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740051, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) UK's initial demand for total allowable catch and (b) agreed outcome was for quotas for each species in its negotiations with the EU on fish quotas in each year since 2021", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740048, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9277 on Home Office: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in her Department's headquarters in London; and how many individual d", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740047, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9277 on Home Office: Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in her Department\u2019s headquarters office in the most recent four weeks for ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740046, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9068 on Department for Education: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in her Department's headquarters in London; and how many individua", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740045, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9068 on Department for Education: Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in her Department\u2019s headquarters office in the most recent four weeks f", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740044, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 9607 on DBT: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in his Department's headquarters in London; and how many individual desks are ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740043, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 9607 on DBT: Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in his Department\u2019s headquarters in the most recent four weeks for which figures ar", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740042, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 9617 on DEFRA: Buildings, how many civil servants are assigned to work in his Department's headquarters in London; and how many in", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740041, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024, to Question 9617, on DEFRA: Buildings, how many individual desks were occupied in his Department\u2019s HQ office in the most recent four weeks fo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740040, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of increasing the pupil premium for (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740039, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of the updated 2024-2025 Nuvaxovid\u2122 COVID-19 Vaccine.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740037, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if she will strengthen the procedure ensuring that patients meet the residency requirements for treatment on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740036, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to trial new accessible voting devices to help blind and partially sighted people vote independently.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740035, "askingMemberId": 5282, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department is providing funding to ensure the future viability of the 84B bus route.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740033, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his planned timeline is for bringing the Armed Forces Covenant fully into law.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740030, "askingMemberId": 5107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that contract negotiations take into account variations in unit prices between dentistry practices (a) across England and (b) that are geographically c", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740029, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will review the postal voting system to help improve accessibility for blind and partially sighted people.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740028, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13037", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Equality Act 2010 in improving services for people with disabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740027, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department is taking steps to recover costs incurred by local authorities in maintaining the safety, security and environmental integrity of the property portfolio or", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740026, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department plans to take support community-based volunteering opportunities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740224, "askingMemberId": 4654, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle persistent nuisance parking on public highways.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740223, "askingMemberId": 4654, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to re-introduce the moratorium on allowing the development of incinerators to go ahead; and what his policy is when an incinerator project has received pla", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740222, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that concentrations of per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances are within the guideline levels set by the Drinking Water Inspectorate.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740221, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies on animal welfare of the use of cages in farming.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740220, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that abattoirs adhere to animal welfare requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740219, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to help support low income households with their energy bills.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740218, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Myanmar on upholding human rights in that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740217, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on allowing humanitarian assistance to be delivered in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740216, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of dynamic pricing on the accessibility of music gigs.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740215, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "13025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of providing a list of LGBTQ+ friendly travel destinations in travel guidance to British citizens.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740214, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to review the prescription charge exemption list.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740213, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help support (a) older applicants, (b) non-English speakers and (c) digitally excluded people to apply for e-visas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740212, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make an assessment with Cabinet colleagues of the potential impact of the changes made to inheritance tax at the Autumn Budget 2024 on the financial viability of small family farms in the north east o", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740211, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of private companies that manage NHS car parks.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740210, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of Blue Badge parking spaces at NHS facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740209, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the impact of changes to inheritance tax on the Scottish economy.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740208, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will eliminate parking fees at NHS hospitals for NHS staff and patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740207, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to tackle landlords charging high up-front rent payments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740206, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the supply of socially rented homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740205, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support children in kinship care.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740204, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman entitled Women\u2019s State Pension age: our findings on injustice and associated issues, published on 21 March 2024, HC 638, if", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740203, "askingMemberId": 4831, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the government is taking to improve animal welfare.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740197, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to promote (a) Scotch whisky exports and (b) other Scottish exports.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740196, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Animal Health and Welfare Pathway in encouraging cage free systems of farming.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740194, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timetable is for announcing further grants through the animal health and welfare pathway.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740186, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help increase the early diagnosis rate for bowel cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740185, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to expand Fracture Liaison Services in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740184, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-14T00:00:00", "uin": "13007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the number of statutory maternity pay cases per constituency in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, and (d) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740182, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take at COP29 to help mitigate the impact of climate change on global religious minorities.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740181, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Pakistani counterpart on reversing anti-blasphemy legislation.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740170, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "13004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when the Government plans to publish its findings from research into the potential costs of geothermal heat in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740168, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his department has plans to increase funding for (a) NGOs and (b) human rights defenders operating in Afghanistan who are promoting the human rights of (i) women, (ii", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740144, "askingMemberId": 4981, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to tackle rural crime in Lancashire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740130, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 12092 on Spain: Floods, how many British citizens have been affected by floods in Spain.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740125, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "13000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support businesses to transition away from plastic.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740124, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of endocrine-disrupting chemicals in plastic (a) products and (b) packaging on human health.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740122, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to publish a schedule of plastic bans.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740117, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing grants to housing associations to buy back homes from shared ownership leaseholders unable to sell their homes", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740115, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of an industrial strategy for offshore wind.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740113, "askingMemberId": 4667, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of continuing grant funding to the offshore wind supply chain investment.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740095, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) asylum seekers and (b) refugees are studying degree courses at universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740091, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with health charities on the potential impact of increases in levels of employers' national insurance contributions on those charities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740090, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of an increase in employers national insurance contributions on dental practices' finances.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740089, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will reintroduce\u00a0the Equipment Theft (Prevention) Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740087, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to raise the default minimum accessibility requirement to the M4(2) Accessible and Adaptable standard for all new residential buildings.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740086, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) creating a Gaza Family visa scheme modelled on the Ukraine Family Scheme visa and (b) deferring biometric requirements for those eligible ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740069, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 October 2024 to Question 6540 on Kidney Diseases: Transplant Surgery, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of providing psychological and social care suppor", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740068, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Office of Budget Responsibility on increasing (a) university tuition fees and (b) maximum maintenance loan levels.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740067, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increasing the maximum level of maintenance loan that students can take out on public sector net (a) debt and (b) financial liabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740066, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of an increase in university tuition fees have on public sector net (a) debt and (b) financial liabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740064, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve maternity services in (a) Slough constituency and (b) Berkshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740063, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740062, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12982", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740061, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740060, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12980", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740059, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740058, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740057, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740056, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740055, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740054, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740053, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740052, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps they are taking to use (a) artificial intelligence and (b) data to help increase their Department's productivity.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740049, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support local businesses in (a) Slough constituency and (b) Berkshire to access (i) funding and (ii) incentives for local net-zero projects.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740202, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps the UK Space Agency to help develop high-skilled jobs in the space sector; and whether the agency supports (a) apprenticeships and (b) development programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740201, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to support the Scottish space sector; and whether his Department provides support for UK entities bidding for European Space Agency contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740200, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the UK's commitments under investor-state dispute settlement mechanisms on (a) environmental and (b) human rights protections in partner countri", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740199, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of the investor-state dispute settlement measures in the Colombia-UK Bilateral Investment Treaty on the upholding o", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740198, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Colombian counterpart on the UK-Colombia Bilateral Investment Treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740195, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the scotch whisky industry on barriers to business.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740193, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the increase in alcohol duty on scotch whisky exports.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740192, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of increases in the duty on non-draught alcohol on levels of employment in the scotch whisky industry.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740191, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of increases on the duty for non-draught alcohol on the scotch whisky industry.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740190, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he next plans to meet the Scotch Whisky Association.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740189, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12960", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of HMRC's processing of refund requests for taxpayers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740188, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the impact of the proposed increase in national insurance contributions on general practices in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740183, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Environment Agency's paper entitled, A summary of England\u2019s revised draft regional and water resources management plans, published on 21 March 2024, whether he ha", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740180, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the formula used to allocate flood funding to rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740179, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12956", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to review Public Works Loan Board rates offered to councils.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740178, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to renew the Community Housing Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740177, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to reform funding arrangements for Internal Drainage Board levies.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740176, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will provide additional support to district councils to reduce levels of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740175, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans she has to include district councils in the Suffolk devolution deal.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740174, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff members will be employed in the National Armament Director\u2019s private office.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740173, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where he plans to locate the private office of the National Armaments Director.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740172, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he categorises the National Armaments Director role as a (a) civil servant or (b) military appointment.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740171, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12948", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding she has budgeted (a) overall and (b) for each Department to reimburse them for the increased costs they incur from the rise in employers national insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740167, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when members of the Immediate Choice veterans cohort will receive their McCloud remedy pension payments.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740164, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many assessments for destitution her Department made for people subject to no recourse to public funds conditions in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740162, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of (a) increases to the Energy Profits Levy and (b) the abolition of the investment allowance on future trends of private investment in north east Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740161, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12944", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of proposed increases to the Energy Profits Levy on future employment levels in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740160, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12943", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of proposed increases to the Energy Profits Levy on supply chain resilience.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740159, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of (a) increases to the Energy Profits Levy and (b) the abolition of the investment allowance on north east Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740158, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of an increase in the rate of employers' National Insurance C", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740157, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has made on tackling unregulated cosmetic procedures; and whether he plans to follow up on the previous Government's consultation on that matter.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740137, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what assessment he has made with Cabinet colleagues of the potential impact of the proposed increase in the rate ", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740169, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12938", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 4 November 2024 to Question 11881 on Research Finance, if her Department will publish a tabular summary of Capital DEL allocated in the Budget to research and development by Department for\u00a0", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740166, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people in Staffordshire have not yet been paid compensation for land and properties compulsorily purchased by HS2 Ltd.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740165, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people have not yet been paid compensation for land and properties compulsorily purchased by HS2 Ltd.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740110, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "12935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the number of (a) car rental car parking spaces and (b) car rental car parking spaces with electric charging points at each airport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740107, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public electric vehicle charging points there are in each local authority area on (a) local authority land and (b) privately owned land.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740102, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "12933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) petrol, (b) diesel, (c) hybrid and (d) electric (i) cars, (ii) vans and (iii) other vehicles his Department hired in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740099, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "12932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many (a) petrol, (b) diesel, (c) hybrid and (d) electric (i) cars, (ii) vans and (iii) other vehicles his Department hired in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740096, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on Great British Railways Decarbonisation plan.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740094, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on Network Rail's Traction Decarbonisation Network Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740093, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the Government's Rail freight Growth Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740092, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on (a) the Folkestone to Wembley Rail Freight route and (b) adopting the gauge to W12 for cross-channel rail freight.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740050, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 11248 on Coronavirus: Vaccination, what discussions the MHRA has had with industry safety regulators on the potential implications of the Pfize", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740038, "askingMemberId": 4088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make a comparative assessment of UK and EU product standard regulations issued since 31 January 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740034, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12925", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments considers direct ministerial appointments from the civil service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740032, "askingMemberId": 4040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has undertaken research into the prevalence of chronic traumatic encephalopathy in (a) professional athletes and (b) recreational players of sport.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740031, "askingMemberId": 4040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions her Department has had with stakeholders on helping to reduce the prevalence of chronic traumatic encephalopathy amongst sportspeople.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740187, "askingMemberId": 1536, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of Wednesday 6 November to Questions 12253, 12254, 12255 and 12256 on Government Hospitality: Wines and Government Hospitality: Spirits, who the attend", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740121, "askingMemberId": 1171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to Section 1.3 2. of the UK-US Atlantic Declaration, what progress he has made on (a) enabling the UK and US export controls toolkits to work in a complementary way, (b) implementing exp", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740119, "askingMemberId": 1171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12920", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to the policy paper entitled The Atlantic Declaration, updated on 21 June 2023, who is the lead (a) minister and (b) official for (i) a shared workplan on critical and emerging technologies, (ii) collaborative Res", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740118, "askingMemberId": 1171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12919", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to the policy paper entitled The Atlantic Declaration, updated on 21 June 2023, what progress he has made on (a) a shared workplan on critical and emerging technologies, (b) collaborative Research and Development ", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740108, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Economy Minister on using Northern Ireland's ultra fast broadband capability to expand the business sector.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740100, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when the first meeting of InterTrade UK will take place.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740098, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "12916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) petrol, (b) diesel, (c) hybrid and (d) electric (i) cars, (ii) vans and (iii) other vehicles her Department hired in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740071, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12915", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11832 on Living Wage, how many and what proportion of workers affected by the increase in the National Living Wage will become taxpayers in April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740120, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make it her policy to immediately deport foreign nationals convicted of criminal offences resulting in custodial sentences.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740109, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish an Equality Impact Assessment of changes resulting from the Elections Act 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740088, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of how many miles of pylons and power lines will need to be built in England to meet the 2030 clean power target.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740065, "askingMemberId": 1171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the cost is of legal fees related to Post Office IT Horizon redress paid to external law firms by (a) scheme and (b) firm.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740163, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of alternative sites for the prospective relocation of the Chinese Embassy, aside from the proposed developm", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1740225, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 4.44 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, whether any of the additional funding allocated to the BBC World Service will go towards BBC Moni", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1740225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739791, "askingMemberId": 5180, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of regulating micro-mobility modes of transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739790, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential feasibility of extending free prescriptions to care leavers aged 18 to 25.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739789, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12906", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential economic impact of the export procedures mandated by Section 45B (1) of the United Kingdom Internal Market Act 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739788, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12905", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of goods moving from Northern Ireland to Great Britain subject to the export procedures mandated by Section 45B (1) of the United Kingdom Internal Market Act 2", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739787, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12904", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, (a) where and (b) how the checks on goods moving from Northern Ireland to Great Britain under the export procedures mandated by Section 45B (1) of the United Kingdom Internal Market Act 2020 will take place.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739786, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12903", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what export procedures will apply to goods moving from Northern Ireland to Great Britain in relation to each of the areas where export procedures are mandated by Section 45B (1) of the United Kingdom Internal Market", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739785, "askingMemberId": 5308, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 10824 on Instagram: Politics and Government, if he will ask Ofcom to investigate Instagram's limiting of political content.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739784, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to designate (a) Fire and Rescue services, (b) the Environment Agency and (c) the Health and Safety Executive as statutory consultees in the planning process fo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739783, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11395 on Undocumented Migrants: Offenders, if she will publish information on the proportion of irregular migrants who have (a) previous criminal ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739782, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12899", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the export procedures required in relation to the movement of goods from Northern Ireland to Great Britain under the areas specified by Section 45B (1) of the United Kingdom Internal Market Act 2020 come into e", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739781, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Universal Credit reimbursement processes on claimants having to pay childcare fees upfront in a lump sum.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739780, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure contracts made between the NHS and private providers aren't acquired by private equity companies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739779, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to end badger culling.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739778, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to improve safety on rural roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739777, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to clear up water ways in Ashford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739776, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2024 to Question 9069 on Department for Education: Ministers' Private Offices, if she will publish the invoice for the new chairs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739775, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2024 to Question 9281 on Department for Transport: Ministers' Private Offices, if she will publish the invoices for the work done.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739774, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12891", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2024 to Question 9827 on Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Ministers' Private Offices, how much the Government Property Agency spent on (a) new furniture and", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739773, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12890", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2024 to Question 9615 on Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Ministers' Private Offices, how much the Government Property Agency spent on (a) new furniture and fitti", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739772, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 9269 on Ministry of Justice: Ministers\u2019 Private Offices, if she will publish the invoices for the work done.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739771, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help support unsustainable debt burdens and service payments from countries in Africa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739770, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help improve the lives of the Hazara population in Aghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739769, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the treatment of the Hazara population in Afghanistan by the Taliban.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739768, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support is available for victims of repeated sexual offences by the same perpetrator.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739767, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the number of registered sex offenders subject to restrictions on internet use who have obtained unrestricted internet access in the last two years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739766, "askingMemberId": 5101, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the number of times that registered sex offenders have (a) attempted to change and (b) been prevented from changing their name by legal means in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739765, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the clean air policy addresses the risks of (a) carbon monoxide and (b) other indoor air pollutants.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739764, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of lifting the two-child benefit cap on funding for local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739728, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending funding settlements for the Household Support Fund beyond one year.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739727, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the rise in the rate of employer national in", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739725, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that teachers have the (a) classroom support and (b) equipment needed to support pupils with SEND.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739724, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will meet with the hon. Member for Tiverton and Minehead to discuss a case of international child abduction.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739723, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report entitled Budget 2024 Briefing, published by Tech First in October 2024, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of levels of child poverty on resource allocation in sch", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739715, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of uprating the state pension for British pensioners residing overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739714, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support British state pensioners residing overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739711, "askingMemberId": 5117, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12873", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to review import duty.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739703, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12872", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to (a) respond to the recommendations of the Infected Blood Inquiry and (b) involve people affected by infected blood.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739702, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many irregular migrants were housed in hotels of each star rating in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739701, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of Universal Credit were born outside the UK in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739699, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS IVF treatments were provided to asylum seekers in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739698, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2024 to Question 11207 on Habitual Residence Test, how many habitual residence tests related to Universal Credit assessments have been granted in each of the last fi", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739696, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will (a) hold discussions with the Sentencing Council on the adequacy of sentencing guidelines for people who have been convicted of wildlife crimes and (b) make an assessment of the potential implications", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739694, "askingMemberId": 5166, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will bring forward regulations to ensure that solar panels fitted to new housing are (a) safe and (b) pose a low fire risk.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739693, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12865", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to allow (a) churches and (b) other religious buildings to continue to recover VAT.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739691, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will (a) approve and (b) deliver rail infrastructure upgrades (i) in the Ely area and (ii) at Haughley Junction.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739690, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will ensure that (a) audio and (b) tactile solutions are available at polling stations to enable (i) blind and (ii) partially sighted voters to vote (A) indepen", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739685, "askingMemberId": 5118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding the Women's and Children's Hospital in Milton Keynes has received up to the end of the 2023/24 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739683, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12861", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of how many farms in Wales will be affected by the changes to agricultural property relief in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739682, "askingMemberId": 5118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the new Women's and Children's Hospital in Milton Keynes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739677, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the financial information provided by Petroineos; and what discussions he has had with Petroineos on that information.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739672, "askingMemberId": 5176, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) specialist support teaching assistants and (b) teachers of sensory impairment with a full mandatory qualification in sensory impairment are employed in (i) England, (ii) Derbyshire County Council a", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739670, "askingMemberId": 5315, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has had discussions with North Northamptonshire Council on school transport fees.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739665, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12856", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will have discussions with the Royal Household on the administration of the Duchies of (a) Cornwall and (b) Lancaster.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739664, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to improve employment regulation applicable to (a) Deliveroo, (b) Just Eat and (c) other online food delivery companies.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739663, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to reduce waiting times for driving tests in South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739660, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the (a) adequacy of and (b) potential merits of undertaking a review of provider access legislation for students with SEND to assist them with acquiring employment.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739659, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure parents have access to the materials used to teach their children in (a) relationships, sex and health education, (b) religious education and (c) other lessons.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739658, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had recent discussions with her French counterpart on the potential merits of preventing small boats from crossing the Channel by intercepting them mid-journey.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739656, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to publish a response to the consultation entitled Transitional support mechanism for large-scale biomass electricity generators, published on 18 January 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739655, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure local authorities have equal access to funding for special educational needs and disabilities services.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739653, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12848", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to provide additional funding to GPs for the cost of the increase in employers' National Insurance Contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739652, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of taking steps to encourage rural off-grid households to switch to hydrogenated vegetable oil in heating.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739651, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many National Insurance Numbers were issued to (a) Bulgarian and (b) Romanian nationals in Boston and Skegness constituency in each year since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739647, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12845", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the amount of Russian assets held by sanctioned individuals in the UK; and how much and what proportion of those assets have been recovered.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739642, "askingMemberId": 5127, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to introduce prostate cancer testing for men at earlier ages than is currently available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739641, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of housing asylum seekers who have arrived on small boats in (a) hotels and (b) other locations since January 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739640, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have (a) applied for and (b) received a Veterans' ID Card in (a) South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency and (b) Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739639, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12841", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many estates were subject to inheritance tax in South Norfolk constituency in the (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-21 and (c) 2021-22 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739638, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of workers that will be affected by the increase to the (a) National Minimum Wage and (b) National Living Wage in Norfolk.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739637, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many and what proportion of workers aged above 16 years old are paid within 50p of the (a) National Minimum Wage and (b) National Living Wage in (i) East Anglia and (ii) Norfolk.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739635, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12838", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many heat pumps are installed on Government property.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739634, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of a devolution deal for Norfolk on (a) local housing supply and (b) economic growth.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739633, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of building a new settlement in Norfolk.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739632, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding that will be allocated to NHS services in Norfolk in each of the n", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739630, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support homeless military veterans in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739629, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to allocate new (a) funding and (b) resources to support children with special educational needs and disabilities in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739628, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to support bus services in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739626, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of GPs in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739625, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12830", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of fatalities on roads in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739624, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of foreign national offenders have successfully appealed a deportation order under Article (a) 3, (b) 6 and (c) 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights, in each year ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739623, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of irregular migrants were (a) in Essex and (b) housed in hotels in Essex in the last 12 months; and how many of those have been removed since October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739622, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on refugee integration loans in each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739621, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the level of foreign aid for India.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739620, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of undertaking a pay review for all military personnel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739619, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on reducing waiting lists for planned care in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739618, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help improve mental health services in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739617, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce shoplifting in Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739616, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on tackling knife crime in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739615, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make it his policy to increase the variety of ownership amongst large breweries in the public sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739614, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase competition in the (a) pub and (b) breweries sector in Wokingham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739613, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help promote the growth of independent brewers in Wokingham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739602, "askingMemberId": 5119, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve access to youth services.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739601, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing overseas constituencies for elections to the House of Commons.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739599, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12815", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, if she will make it her policy to exempt hospices from the increase in employers\u2019 National Insurance Contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739598, "askingMemberId": 5119, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle antisocial behaviour in (a) Croydon East constituency and (b) other constituencies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739597, "askingMemberId": 5119, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the police have adequate resources to tackle knife crime in (a) Croydon East constituency and (b) other constituencies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739596, "askingMemberId": 5119, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the potential impact of the policies to be set out in the Get Britain Working white paper on the number of people who will be supported back into work in each region.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739595, "askingMemberId": 5119, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of (a) children and (b) young people that are waiting for mental health support.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739587, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department provides free English lessons for irregular migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739586, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has undertaken an evaluation of the Mid-life MOT initiative.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Advisory Services: Older Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739585, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "uin": "12808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department made of the number of cases of avian influenza within the game bird population.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avian Influenza", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739565, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-07T00:00:00", "uin": "12807", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his expected timetable is for the publication of an updated list of significant public appointments; and whether this will include the Chair of the Office for Environmental Protection.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739763, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she an estimate of the cost of providing all care leavers in England with the over 25 rate of Universal Credit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739762, "askingMemberId": 5000, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits of making prostate cancer screening mandatory.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739761, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made on the impact that the national insurance increase will have on the cost of paid-for childcare.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739760, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing funding rates for (a) public and (b) privat", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739759, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what estimate she has made of the potential impact of the rise in the rate of employer national insurance contri", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739758, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2024 to Question 11294 on Armed Forces: Cadets, what discussions she had with the Minister for Veterans and People on the School staff instructor grant.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739757, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will include bespoke support for unemployed care leavers in the Youth Guarantee.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739756, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of an enhanced financial support package for care leavers aged 18 to 25.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739755, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Healthy Ageing Challenge in helping companies scale up projects.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739754, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of UKRI funding in helping innovative projects scale-up.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739753, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Accelerating Reform Fund in innovating the social care sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739752, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the accessibility of Universal Credit for farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739751, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on (a) farming and (b) flood funding for the remainder of this Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739750, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much Local Power plan funding will be allocated between each of the UK nations.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739748, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps they are taking to help increase productivity within their Department through the use of (a) artificial intelligence and (b) effective use of data.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739747, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to help increase productivity within his Department through the use of (a) artificial intelligence and (b) effective use of data.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739746, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to help increase productivity within his Department through the use of (a) artificial intelligence and (b) effective use of data.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739744, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12789", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of access to hormone replacement therapies for women experiencing the menopause.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739743, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of training for GPs to (a) diagnose and (b) treat women experiencing the menopause.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739740, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of placing restrictions on marriage between first cousins.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739737, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve retention rates in his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739736, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve retention rates in the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739735, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve retention rates in the Royal Air Force.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739734, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve retention rates in the Royal Navy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739733, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve retention rates in the Army.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739732, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12781", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including the potential risks associated with not fully rebuilding the Animal Plant and Health Agency Headquarters in Weybridge in the National Risk Regis", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739731, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November to Question 11902 on Import Controls: Port of Dover, when checks on animals at Border Control Posts will begin.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739729, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he taking to help increase productivity within his Department through the use of (a) artificial intelligence and (b) effective use of data.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739722, "askingMemberId": 5084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to make it easier for women to report abuse experienced when they have been exercising in public.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739720, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of automated external defibrillators in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739717, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to support (a) hospices, (b) GPs and (c) care homes, in the context of proposed changes to employer National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739713, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12775", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a phased approach to stamp duty increases for those in pre-agreed property transactions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739712, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing student maintenance loans in line with Consumer Price Index inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739710, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to work with local authorities to enforce noise curfews during fireworks.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739709, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2024 to Question 8195, on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: HOPE not hate, what the forums were at which departmental of", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739708, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 30 October 2024, to Question 10945, on Home Office: HOPE not hate, what meetings officials who are not classified as senior officials for the purposes of quarterly transparen", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739707, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria the Prevent programme uses to (a) identify and (b) define subcategories of Extreme Right-Wing Terrorism.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739695, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12769", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she plans to implement Section 14 of the Finance Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739680, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12768", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she made a socio-economic impact assessment of the increase to employer national insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739678, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing surpluses to the British Coal Staff Superannuation Scheme in line with the Mineworkers\u2019 Pension Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739676, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.72 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, whether she plans to hold a consultation on the rolling stock strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739675, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12765", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.30 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, whether she plans to hold a consultation on the proposed Infrastructure Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739673, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when she plans to publish guidance on the Leasehold and Freehold Reform Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739669, "askingMemberId": 4873, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assistance his Department has offered to the Spanish government, in the context of recent floods in that country.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739668, "askingMemberId": 5001, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many roadside inspections on Operator License Operated Mini Buses have been undertaken in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739667, "askingMemberId": 5001, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) school and (b) other minibuses have failed inspections under Section 19 of the Transport Act 1985 in the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739666, "askingMemberId": 4846, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12760", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to employer National Insurance contribution rates on GPs in Northern Ireland; and whether s", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739662, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children with with epilepsy have individual healthcare plans.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739657, "askingMemberId": 5033, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the small modular reactor competition run by Great British Nuclear, whether his Department is taking other steps to support the development of privately (a) funded and (b) o", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739650, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the rate of return to public investment in UK R&D.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739649, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of R&D investment in (a) clean energy, (b) AI and (c) quantum technology on (i) the University of Nottingham and (ii) Nottingham Tren", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739648, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve care for people with migraines.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739627, "askingMemberId": 5044, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has had with the UK Atomic Energy Authority on ensuring that expertise gained through the Joint European Torus (JET) experiment is (a) retained and (b) used by the UK STEP", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739612, "askingMemberId": 5076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department issues guidance on (a) identifying and (b) tackling political interference from international actors to academic institutions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739611, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted for making hoax calls to the emergency services in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739610, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce instances of post traumatic stress disorder within the (a) police and (b) fire service.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739609, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to reduce instances of post traumatic stress disorder within the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739603, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12749", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the note entitled Allowance for impact on public sector organisations in Table 5.1 on page 118 of Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, if she will publish this information by D", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739600, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Elections Act 2022 on overseas voting.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739594, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12747", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has prepared terms of reference for a consultation on replacing business rates with a land value tax since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739593, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12746", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2024 to Question 9564 on Employers' Contributions: Small Businesses, if she will publish any impact assessment for the raise to employer National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739574, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, following the Chancellor's commitment of \u00a33 billion a year for the Ukraine war effort, what similar commitment does this budget make for our continued support of Israel's war effort.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739573, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include the South Fylde Passing Loop Project in new rail infrastructure spending.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "South Fylde Line: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739561, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when her Department plans to publish the prospectus on the Long-Term Plan for Towns.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739749, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for pension credit there were from 28t October 2024 to 4 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739721, "askingMemberId": 4399, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12741", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department\u2019s publication entitled Summary of reforms to agricultural property relief and business property relief, published on 30 October 2024, how many Agricultural Property Relief claims in ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739716, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2024 to Question 11939 on Ministry of Defence: Employers' Contributions, whether the \u00a3216 million figure given is the (a) direct cost of his Department\u2019s Ministry of Defence: ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739706, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the World Food Programme and Food and Agriculture Organisation of the United Nations' report on Hunger Hotspots June to October 2024, published in June 2024", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739705, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the World Food Programme and Food and Agriculture Organisation of the United Nations' report on Hunger Hotspots June to October 2024, published in June 2024", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739704, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the World Food Programme and Food and Agriculture Organisation of the United Nations' report on Hunger Hotspots June to October 2024, published in June 2024", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739700, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department have taken to introduce a Deposit Return Scheme for plastic bottles.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739681, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the average wait for a Personal Independence Payment review decision.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739679, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to (a) advise claimants migrating to Universal Credit from legacy benefits to check whether their eligibility for NHS Help with Health Costs will change and (b) include this advic", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739671, "askingMemberId": 4409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-19T00:00:00", "uin": "12733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to prevent (a) parking debt collectors and (b) legal firms from adding \u00a370 to existing parking charges of \u00a3100 per PCN; and whether she plans to ban debt r", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739631, "askingMemberId": 4277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to automatically enrol eligible families in the NHS Healthy Start programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739608, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce instances of post traumatic stress disorder within the ambulance service.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739607, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the impact on the NHS from individuals who repeatedly misuse emergency ambulance services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739606, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost is of hoax calls made to the (a) police and (b) fire service.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739605, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to improve information sharing between emergency services on hoax callers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739604, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help reduce the number of hoax calls to the emergency services.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739590, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help support (a) religious tolerance and (b) the Rohingya people in (i) Myanmar and (ii) Bangladesh.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739582, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce regulatory requirements for food exporters trading with the EU.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739581, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of making an assessment of (a) core food and drink production standards, (b) environmental sustainability and (c) animal welfare standard before co", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739580, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will hold discussions with representatives of the food and drink industry on the impact of their products on public health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739579, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to announce the (a) fees and (b) invoicing periods for the extended producer responsibility scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739578, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to provide regular information to businesses on how revenues raised through the extended producer responsibility scheme are spent by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739576, "askingMemberId": 4493, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2024 to Question 6280 on Gaza: Air Force, whether his Department used information from the Ministry of Defence on unarmed UK surveillance", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739575, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any funds raised through the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 have not been distributed in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739571, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department provides for research on rare genetic disorders.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739570, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Darfur.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739569, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will have discussions with his counterparts in Northern Ireland on potential steps to facilitate the provision of records from mother and baby homes in Northern Ireland to affected individuals.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739568, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle the sexual exploitation of women to pay drug debts.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739567, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans he has for the provision of support to Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739566, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an estimate of the amount of money (a) spent and (b) lost on illegal gambling sites in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739563, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to increase public awareness of pancreatic cancer symptoms.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739562, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of trends in the level of maternal health inequalities affecting black women.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739742, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12710", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to point 28 of Table 5.1 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, whether unmarried couples will be liable for inheritance tax on Death-in-Service benefits over \u00a3325,000 payabl", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739741, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes to Inheritance Tax announced in the Autumn Budget 2024 on levels of production of the five key crops by tonnage in the ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739739, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the proportion of farm holdings that are owned by a single person or entity.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739738, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of farm holdings that are estimated to have a net value of (a) between \u00a31,000,000 and \u00a31,499,999, (b) between \u00a31,500,000 and \u00a31,999,", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739726, "askingMemberId": 4018, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps through the National Planning Policy Framework to support local authorities with assessing the cumulative impact of multiple planning applications on (a) s", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739719, "askingMemberId": 4088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an estimate of the number of EU product standard regulations that will be issued in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739718, "askingMemberId": 4088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many officials in his Department have worked on product standard regulations in each year since 31 January 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739692, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12703", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the (a) effectiveness of the Well-being of Future Generations (Wales) Act 2015 and (b) potential merits of adopting that legislation nationwide.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739592, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12702", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department\u2019s policies of recommendation 3 of His Majesty\u2019s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire & Rescue Services' report on An inspection into activism a", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739591, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12701", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent guidance the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments has provided to special envoys on lobbying.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739589, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12700", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to make a submission to the Civil Service Commission review of appointments made by exception at delegated grades.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739588, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what is the cost of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme; and when she plans to make a decision on the renewal of that scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739584, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12698", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make a comparative estimate of the average cost of (a) VAT, (b) employers' National Insurance contributions, (c) contributions to the Teachers' Pensions Scheme and (d) business rates for independent scho", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739583, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12697", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of increases in employers\u2019 National Insurance contributions on (a) cost pressures for independent schools and (b) the number of children leaving ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739572, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2024 to Question 4203 on Primodos: Research, when he expects the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency to complete that review; and what steps h", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739564, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the level of compliance with the Immediate Prohibition Notices issued to (a) SSE Renewables and (b) Petrofac Facilities Management on 6 September 2024 by the Hea", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739697, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals released from prison in 2023 and deported have subsequently returned to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739689, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were fined for not microchipping their (a) cats and (b) dogs in each year since 2016.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739688, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to support Havering Council to enhance (a) the River Rom's environmental health, (b) maintenance of river-based infrastructure and (c) development of projects aim", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739687, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time for an NHS dental practice is in Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739686, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to reduce the backlog in the administration of warrants for possession.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739684, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS patients have been treated with Spinraza in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) the East Midlands since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739661, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have (a) been recruited and (b) left their roles since 2014.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739577, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Ofcom on (a) allegations that Channel One Russia Worldwide has breached the conditions of its TLCS licence and (b) the imposition of statutory sanctions on GB Ne", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739646, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12686", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department conducted an impact assessment on the proposed change on inheritance tax for agricultural properties.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739645, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve the recruitment of male primary school teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739644, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help improve ambulance response times in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739643, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for a dementia assessment in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739745, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will raise the detention in Azerbaijan of Dr. Gubad Ibadoghlu during COP29 climate conference in November.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739730, "askingMemberId": 40, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he plans to implement a British jobs bonus scheme; and how much he plans to allocate to each year of the scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739500, "askingMemberId": 5337, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people living with dementia in Reading West and Mid Berkshire constituency received a (a) care plan review and (b) new care plan in financial year 2023/24.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dementia: Reading West and Mid Berkshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739499, "askingMemberId": 5337, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time for a dementia assessment is in Reading West and Mid Berkshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dementia: Reading West and Mid Berkshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739498, "askingMemberId": 5337, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people are waiting for an appointment with a Memory Assessment Service for a dementia assessment in Reading West and Mid Berkshire constituency as of 4 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dementia: Reading West and Mid Berkshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739496, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report entitled \u00a32 bus fare cap evaluation: interim report, published on 17 May 2023, if her Department will publish the final report.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739495, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will dual the A47 from Tilney to East Winch.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A47: Dual Carriageways", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739492, "askingMemberId": 5315, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12674", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to help protect British businesses in (a) the hobby sector and (b) other sectors from (i) TEMU and (ii) other cheap import companies.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Imports: Companies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739489, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what data his Department holds on the number of lorries turned away at Northern Ireland ports for carrying cargo incorrectly listed on their manifests.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Internal Trade: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739488, "askingMemberId": 5282, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will create alternative qualification pathways for students with Education, Health and Care Plans to support their access to further education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Further Education: Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739467, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12671", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking with HMRC to help ensure taxpayers receive prompt responses to queries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Revenue and Customs: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739463, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure super trawlers report marine mammal by-catch to the Marine Management Organisation.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Animals: Fishing Catches", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739458, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the new Border Target Operating Model (a) generally and (b) at tackling the illegal import of products of animal origin.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739457, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support social workers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739456, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Immediate measures to step up safeguards against African swine fever from Europe, published on 26 September 2024, to help prev", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739454, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled African swine fever: how to spot and report the disease, updated on 27 September 2024, whether he plans to ban all personal imports", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739453, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) likelihood of an African Swine Fever outbreak in the UK and (b) economic impact of such an outbreak.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739442, "askingMemberId": 5276, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on the development of a clinical policy relating to the use of abiraterone acetate as a first-line treatment for men with locally advanced high-risk prostate cancer; and w", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739434, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with ADHD receive the level of support set out in the guidelines by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence entitled Attentio", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739429, "askingMemberId": 5349, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help tackle overcrowding in social housing in (a) Gloucester and (b) England.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Overcrowding", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739427, "askingMemberId": 5349, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effectiveness of legislation in preventing hate crime offences against LGBT+ people in Gloucester constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hate Crime: LGBT+ People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739426, "askingMemberId": 5349, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help tackle violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739425, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12658", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.44 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC295, what the (a) territorial extent and (b) timetable is for the consultation on encouraging small brewers to retain and e", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739424, "askingMemberId": 5349, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the extension of the Household Support Fund in 2025-26 on low-income households in Gloucester.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Household Support Fund: Gloucester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739423, "askingMemberId": 5349, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the average increase in the State Pension in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739422, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has undertaken an evaluation of the Mid-life MOT initiative.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Advisory Services: Older Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739421, "askingMemberId": 5300, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the \u00a310 million allocated to the MHRA in March 2023, what progress has been made on accelerating routes for bringing innovative medical products developed onto the market.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Equipment: Innovation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739420, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12653", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses in Wales will benefit from changes to employment allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739419, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had recent discussions with (a) NHS England, (b) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and (c) the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency on access for p", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alzheimer's Disease: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739418, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will hold discussions with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on the potential merits of considering the potential impact of new treatments on caregivers when determining t", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739417, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.71 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, how many new surgical hubs will focus solely on orthopaedic procedures.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Surgical Hubs: Orthopaedics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739416, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the impact of surgical hubs on waiting times for (a) trauma and (b) orthopaedic treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Surgical Hubs: Injuries and Orthopaedics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739415, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to provide additional funding to (a) community musculoskeletal services and (b) physiotherapy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Musculoskeletal Disorders: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739414, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to provide additional support for people with (a) arthritis and (b) musculoskeletal conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Musculoskeletal Disorders: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739413, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2024 to Question 4786 on Per- and Polyfluorinated Alkyl Substances, what his planned timetable is for considering measures to restrict per- and p", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Per- and Polyfluorinated Alkyl Substances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739412, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will introduce a medal for (a) seriously injured and (b) medically retired service personnel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Decorations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739411, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU migrants (a) transferred from pre-settled status to settled status and (b) were resident in Scotland in 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: EU Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739410, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU migrants transferred from pre-settled status to settled status and were resident in Scotland in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: EU Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739409, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of UK citizenship were made to people resident in Scotland in 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Nationality: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739408, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of UK citizenship were made to people resident in Scotland in 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Nationality: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739407, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of UK citizenship were made to people resident in Scotland in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Nationality: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739406, "askingMemberId": 5254, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12639", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people of state pension age were in receipt of (a) Working and (b) Child Tax Credit in (a) Scarborough and Whitby constituency and (b) North Yorkshire on 4 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739405, "askingMemberId": 5254, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of (a) income-related Employment and Support Allowance, (b) income-based Jobseeker\u2019s Allowance, (c) Income Support, (d) Pension Credit and (e) Universal Credit in (i) Sca", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739404, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were prosecuted for TV licence evasion in England in (a) 2022, (b) 2023 and (c) 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Television Licences: Non-payment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739403, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to increase value for money in procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739402, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps her Department has taken to provide rehabilitation support to children who have lived in care who are (a) in police custody and (b) serving custodial sentences.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children in Care: Young Offenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739401, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of freeports on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Freeports: Economic Situation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739400, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who arrived in the UK by small boats are (a) male and (b) female.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739399, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders of which nationality were deported in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739398, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the affordability of the BBC licence fee for people on lower incomes; and if she will make an assessment of the potential steps she can take to increase the", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Television Licences: Low Incomes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739397, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing an alternative funding scheme to the BBC licence fee.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "BBC: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739396, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the Overseas Development Assistance budget was spent on accommodating asylum seekers in the UK in the most recent year for which figures are available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739395, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential implications for national security of the proportion of funding for universities from China.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739394, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make a comparative assessment of energy prices for steel production in (a) the UK, (b) China, (c) Germany and (d) the US.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Iron and Steel: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739393, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much aid his Department has provided to China in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739392, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that student visas are not used solely to gain residence in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739391, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to support food producers from (a) Essex and (b) the UK to increase exports.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Exports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739390, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help prevent the provision of large dinghies to people smuggling gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Boats", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739389, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of attempted deportations of foreign national offenders by her Department have been successfully challenged on Article 8 ECHR grounds in each of the last ten years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739388, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure decisions on whether to grant Indefinite Leave to Remain under Appendix VDA are made (a) correctly and (b) with reference to appropriate evidence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739387, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter of 22 July 2024 from the hon. member for Henley and Thame about step down beds at Chiltern Court, Henley on Thames.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739386, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will make an estimate of planned defence spending in the next two years as a share of GDP using NATO's definition of defence expenditure.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739385, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the new Get Britain Working Trailblazers will help support people with musculoskeletal conditions to remain in employment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Musculoskeletal Disorders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739384, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Connect to Work scheme will include provisions to support people living with arthritis to remain in employment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme: Arthritis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739383, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much funding his Department plans to provide for research into musculoskeletal treatments in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Musculoskeletal Disorders: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739382, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, whether any of the new surgical hubs will focus solely on orthopaedic procedures.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Surgical Hubs: Orthopaedics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739381, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of surgical hubs on waiting times for (a) trauma and (b) orthopaedic treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Surgical Hubs: Injuries and Orthopaedics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739380, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, how much and what proportion of the additional funding for the NHS will be spent on (a) physiotherapy and (b) other c", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Musculoskeletal Disorders: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739379, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, how much and what proportion of the additional funding for the NHS will be spent on support for people with (a) arthr", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Musculoskeletal Disorders: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739377, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help ensure that victims of rural crime in areas with poor (a) phone and (b) internet coverage are able to report those crimes promptly.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739376, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring NHS Trusts to amalgamate patient data across primary care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primary Health Care: Medical Records", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739497, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will invite representatives of the cruise industry to join the Tourism Industry Council.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739494, "askingMemberId": 5035, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of dropping the salary requirement for people on visas employed by the Government.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739493, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will review support for parents who will not be entitled to Neonatal Care Leave and Pay because they (a) are self-employed and (b) have another ineligible employment status.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parental Leave", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739491, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12606", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when her Department plans to set out details of the independent Loan Charge Review.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739490, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12605", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what Barnett Consequential have been calculated for the Northern Ireland Executive following the recent announcement of additional rates support for (a) retail, (b) hospitality and (c) leisure in the Autumn Budget 2", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739487, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the provision of language support for refugee children in school whose first language is not English.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739486, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to help ensure benefits of technological development are felt by all demographics.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739485, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the safety of (a) women and (b) children online in light of the use of AI in the creation of indecent images; and what discussions she has had with cabi", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739484, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on support for the digitisation of the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739483, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he takes to ensure joint defence projects are compatible with the UK\u2019s (a) arms export control system and (b) international obligations.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739482, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he takes to trace the end-user of UK components delivered to the F-35 programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739481, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had recent discussions with F-35 programme partners on the risk of components supplied to Israel being used to commit violations of international law.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739480, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to extend the Fresh Fruit and Vegetables Aid Scheme after 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Subsidies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739479, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of setting national (a) standards and (b) timescales for repairs to social housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739478, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether the Solar Taskforce plans to take steps to (a) assess the prevalence of and (b) tackle the use of Uyghur forced labour in solar supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739477, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support the long-term funding of Leicestershire Police.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leicestershire Police: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739476, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle puppy smuggling.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Smuggling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739475, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on checking the immigration status of individuals during the process of arrest to prosecution.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Arrests and Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739474, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children requiring SEND support did not attend school in each council ward in Northumberland in each of the last five academic years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Northumberland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739473, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to ensure that people diagnosed with (a) triple negative breast cancer and (b) the BRCA gene mutation are offered genetic counselling.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Genetics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739472, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to test people diagnosed with triple negative breast cancer for the BRCA gene mutation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Genetics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739471, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there are sufficient breast cancer clinical nurse specialists.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Nurses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739470, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to ensure that people with triple negative breast cancer have access to a clinical nurse specialist at the point of diagnosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Nurses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739469, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what level of indemnity is required for each NHS job category.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739468, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, the locations of how many irregular migrants processed by the authorities and believed to be in the UK are unknown to her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739466, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12584", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the total revenue her Department expects to receive from property purchases in London following proposed changes to the rate of stamp duty relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stamp Duty Land Tax: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739465, "askingMemberId": 5209, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12583", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the number of first-time buyers in London that may be subject to stamp duty from April 2025, in the context of proposed changes to the rate of stamp duty relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stamp Duty Land Tax: First Time Buyers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739464, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of raising employer\u2019s National Insurance Contributions on (a) trends in the level of recruitment and (b) the provision of care in the socia", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739462, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what capital funding her Department has allocated to schools in (a) Mid Cheshire constituency, (b) Cheshire and (c) England in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739461, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he takes to ensure UK components supplied to the F-35 programme can be subjected to (a) a product recall and (b) an air accident investigation process .", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739460, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate she has made of the total cost to the public purse of extending HS2 from Old Oak Common to Euston Station.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "High Speed 2 Line: Euston Station", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739459, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he takes to trace the end user of UK components delivered to the F-35 programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739455, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to encourage GPs to proactively discuss (a) prostate cancer risk and (b) the option to have a prostate-specific antigen test with (i) Black men aged 45 and over and (ii) men", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739452, "askingMemberId": 5084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to provide funding for respite care for people with disabilities away from their care setting.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respite Care: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739451, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether irregular migrants housed in hotels have access to (a) pool, (b) gym and (c) other hotel facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739450, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many irregular migrants have crossed the Channel by (a) age and (b) sex in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739449, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12573", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of  the Exchequer, what information her Department holds on the number and proportion of businesses that do not accept cash; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of taking steps to require all businesses to acce", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business: Money", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739448, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) attendances at accident and emergency departments and (b) emergency admissions there were for dentistry-related issues in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Accident and Emergency Departments: Dental Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739447, "askingMemberId": 5093, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12571", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to employer National Insurance contribution rates on third sector organisations; and whether she plans to take steps with Cabinet colleagues to provide", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Civil Society", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739446, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her department's policy is on (a) engines, (b) boats and (c) life jackets recovered from irregular migrant arrivals; and what the cost to the public purse was of the (i) storage of, (ii) destruct", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739445, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to put the Code of Practice for Victims of Crime in England and Wales on a statutory basis.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739444, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that patient (a) experience and (b) voice is reflected in the NHS 10-year plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739443, "askingMemberId": 5000, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of reviewing the Communications Ombudsman's powers to increase the accountability of telecommunications providers.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739441, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase uptake of early screening interventions for chronic kidney disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kidney Diseases: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739440, "askingMemberId": 5060, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how much has been spent on the statutory element of Shared Parental Leave since its inception (a) in total and (b) by (i) geographical area and (ii) industry.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parental Leave", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739439, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many complaints there were about to the standard of English of (a) GPs, (b) consultants and (c) other health care professionals in the NHS in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739438, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on complaints about GPs, broken down by GP nationality, in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739437, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on (a) the number of GP appointments available and (b) excess demand for those appointments in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739436, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he made of the potential implications for his policies of Iran\u2019s (a) compliance with United Nations Security Council resolutions, (b) attempts to develop its ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Iran: Nuclear Weapons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739435, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 11046 on General Practitioners: Finance, when he plans to determine the overall GP contract investment in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739433, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on the number of assets that were bought by community groups through the Community Right to Bid process since its introduction.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739432, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on the number of Assets of Community Value (a) listed by each local authority and (b) rejected by each local authority in the last three yea", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739430, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she ask the Office of Road and Rail to undertake enforcement action against National Highways over ongoing disruption in the (a) Painshill roundabout and (b) local area due to the M25/A3 works.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739428, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, what discussions he has had with health and care charities on the potential impact of increased National Insuran", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739330, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, whether he has made an estimate of the number of GP practices which will close as a result of increased Employer", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739329, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes in employers' National Insurance contributions on Thames Water's (a) financial viability and (b) infrastructure investm", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739328, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which integrated care boards have reimbursed dental practices for up to 110% of General Dental Services contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739323, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12552", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.40 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the potential impact of changes to N", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739322, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many people are in receipt of the Mineworkers Pension Scheme in each constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mineworkers' Pension Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739314, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many social care staff (a) were dismissed and (b) resigned due to mandatory Covid-19 vaccination regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739308, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether any Sri Lankan nationals on Diego Garcia hold criminal records.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739307, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Government of Mauritius in relation to Sri Lankan nationals located on Diego Garcia.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739306, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum claims of Sri Lankan nationals located on Diego Garcia are being considered by her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739305, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans her Department has to continue funding for the Access for All programme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Access", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739304, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of the number and proportion of Sri Lankan nationals located on Diego Garcia that will be eligible to claim asylum in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739295, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the priorities of (a) children and (b) young people with cancer are included in the ten-year plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739294, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for the (a) diagnosis and (b) treatment of cancer in (i) teenagers and (ii) young adults.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739288, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps has her Department is taking with the Teacher's Pension Scheme to reduce the time taken to provide pension valuations for teachers undergoing divorce proceedings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739285, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will include dispute settlement mechanisms on (a) human rights and (b) labour into any Free Trade Agreement with the Gulf Cooperation Council.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Gulf Cooperation Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739284, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of a Free Trade Agreement with the Gulf Cooperation Council on human rights in member states of that council.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Gulf Cooperation Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739283, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, for what reason his Department is pursuing a multilateral free trade agreement with the Gulf Cooperation Council rather than bilateral agreements with the member states.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Gulf Cooperation Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739282, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12538", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of leaving the European (a) Union, (b) Customs Union and (c) Single Market on (i) imports and (ii) exports.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Trade with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739281, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of leaving the European (a) Union, (b) Customs Union and (c) Single Market on food prices.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739280, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps with local partners to ensure the availability of (a) parenting and (b) other programmes to improve the mental health of (i) infants, (ii) children and (iii) young people ment", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739279, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to make wildlife crimes notifiable.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nature Conservation: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739278, "askingMemberId": 5188, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of VAT on private schools on children with special educational needs in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739277, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2024 to Question 9980 on Products: Labelling, if his Department will make an estimate of the number of items of (a) furniture and (b) other products that have been ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Products: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739276, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department made available for school transport for children with Special Educational Needs and Disabilities in academic years (a) 2020-21, (b) 2021-22, (c) 2022-23, (d) 2023-24 and (e) 2024", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739275, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to publish the final evaluation report on the \u00a32 fare cap commissioned by her Department from Frontier Economics and SYSTRA.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739273, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has for the (a) protection and (b) conservation of hedgehogs following the change to their conservation status on the International Union for Conservation of ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hedgehogs: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739272, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to add education on diversity to school curriculums.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739271, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make it his policy to include food systems as a priority within Nationally Determined Contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Climate Change: Food Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739270, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 2.3.2 of the report of the Strategic Dialogue on the Future of EU Agriculture, published on 4 September 2024, what assessment he has made of the potential i", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739269, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that the Advertising Standards Authority upholds standards in relation to pre-watershed online gambling adverts in mobile gaming apps that may b", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gambling: Video Games", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739268, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if his Department will introduce an enforceable liability provision in legislation to ensure that consumers can seek redress for defective products bought via online marketplaces.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739267, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to strengthen the duties of online marketplaces to protect consumers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739265, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of number of beagles needed for use in laboratory experiments in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Animal Experiments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739264, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of beagles being bred for use in laboratory experiments in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Animal Experiments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739263, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps her Department has taken to protect the welfare of beagles bred for sale to animal testing facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dogs: Animal Experiments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739262, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of freezing state pensions on British citizens living overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739261, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support grassroots music venues.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Music Venues: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739253, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of capping single bus fares at \u00a33 in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739252, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made a human rights impact assessment of the transition from Biometric Resident Permits to eVisas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739251, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an equalities impact assessment on the transition from Biometric Resident Permits to eVisas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739244, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of indefinite leave to remain were made to people in the UK on other visa routes whose place of residence was Scotland at the time of grant in 2021; and on what visa statuses they were", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739243, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of indefinite leave to remain were made to people in the UK on other visa routes whose place of residence was Scotland at the time of grant in 2022; and on what visa statuses they were", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739242, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of indefinite leave to remain were made to people in the UK on other visa routes whose place of residence was Scotland at the time of grant in 2023; and on what visa statuses they were", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739241, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of refugee status were made to asylum seekers whose place of residence was Scotland in 2021; and in what type of accommodation they were housed at the time of grant.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739240, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of refugee status were made to asylum seekers whose place of residence was Scotland in 2022; and in what type of accommodation they were housed at the time of grant.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739239, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of refugee status were made to asylum seekers whose place of residence was Scotland in 2023; and in what type of accommodation they were housed at the time of grant.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739238, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family visas were issued where the sponsoring (a) spouse or partner, (b) fianc\u00e9, fianc\u00e9e or proposed civil partner, (c) child, (d) parent and (c) relative providing long-term care was residen", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Dependants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739237, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family visas were issued where the sponsoring (a) spouse or partner, (b) fianc\u00e9, fianc\u00e9e or proposed civil partner, (c) child, (d) parent and (c) relative providing long-term care was residen", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Dependants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739236, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family visas were issued where the sponsoring (a) spouse or partner, (b) fianc\u00e9, fianc\u00e9e or proposed civil partner, (c) child, (d) parent and (c) relative providing long-term care was residen", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Dependants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739235, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many work visas were issued for jobs in Scottish workplaces in 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739234, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many work visas were issued for jobs in Scottish workplaces in Scotland in 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739233, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many work visas were issued for jobs in Scottish workplaces in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739232, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many study visas were issued to students studying at Scottish universities in 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739231, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many study visas were issued to students studying at Scottish universities in 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739230, "askingMemberId": 5245, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many study visas were issued to students studying at Scottish universities in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739229, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with NICE on reducing the time taken for patients to access treatment for very rare diseases in cases when there is uncertainty on the (a) incidence a", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rare Diseases: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739226, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2024 to Question 7596 on Special Educational Needs, how many and what proportion of children who had been excluded from school were then registered at special schools by (a)", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739225, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 14 October to Questions 7569 on Special Educational Needs and 7570 on Pupil Referral Units, how many and what proportion of children who attended Special Educational Needs schools wer", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739224, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2024 to Question 9795 on Pupil Referral Units, if her Department will undertake a manual audit of all children registered at Pupil Referral Units since 1 November 2023 to se", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739223, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2024 to Question 9795 on Pupil Referral Units, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of recording the number of children registered at Pupil Referral Units ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739213, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make it her policy to amend the Sexual Offences Act 2003 to classify driving instructors as a position of trust.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739212, "askingMemberId": 5082, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many Government services have moved to the GOV.UK One Login system; and what his planned timetable is for moving all Government services to this system.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739211, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 1 November 2024 to Question 11117 on Crime: Undocumented Migrants, what information her Department holds on the number of crimes committed by undocumented migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739210, "askingMemberId": 5082, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress she has made on the introduction of digital drivers licences.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Licences: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739209, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many irregular migrants entered the UK in each of the last five years, broken down by vehicle type.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739197, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help improve the (a) accuracy and (b) reliability of personal immigration status information generated by the Government View and Prove system; and what safeguar", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Proof of Identity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739189, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12487", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 31 July 2024 to Question 1207 on Ministers: Media and the Answer of 15 October 2024 to Question 7434 on Political Parties: Donors, whether his Department has issued guidance to Departme", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739188, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12486", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2024 to Question 7430 on the Committee on the Grant of Honours, Decorations and Medals, if he will make an assessment of the current merits of The Most Excellent Order of the", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Order of the British Empire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739187, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12485", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance is available to the partners of Ministers on the acceptance of gifts.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Gifts and Endowments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739186, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his the Prime Minister\u2019s comments on BBC Newscast on 12 October 2024, when did the Government's view on P&O change.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "P&O Ferries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739185, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12483", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the announcement on freeports in October 2024 at the Commonwealth visit, what processes are in place to coordinate policy announcements between Departments and the Prime Minister's office.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Communication", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739176, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of surveys undertaken by the Food Foundation Food entitled Food insecurity tracking, published in July 2024, on a potent", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Poverty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739375, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12481", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the compensation provided to Equitable Life investors via the Equitable Life payment scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equitable Life Assurance Society: Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739374, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12480", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what estimate she has made of the number of owners of working farms in Wales by (a) marital and (b) residency status who will be liable", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739373, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12479", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of changes to (a) inheritance tax, (b) agricultural property relief and (c) busine", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739372, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date her Department sent letters to people eligible for Pension Credit to inform them that they must apply for Pension Credit to continue receiving winter fuel payments.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739371, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department takes to ensure that recall decisions are (a) fair and (b) proportionate to public safety concerns.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Sentences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739370, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department takes to support the reintegration of released prisoners.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739369, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to provide adequate mental health support for prisoners serving Imprisonment for Public Protection sentences.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739367, "askingMemberId": 4637, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to reform Imprisonment for Public Protection sentences.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Sentences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739362, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he plans to publish the terms of reference of the Finucane inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739361, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to paragraph 4.140 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, how much has been allocated to the Finucane inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739353, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on delivering specialist mental health professionals in every school.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Schools", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739352, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12470", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.19 of Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what amount of consequential funding the Welsh Government will receive from the money allocated to local roads maintenanc", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739351, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the judgement in UKSC 2022/0064 on the remaining (a) oil and (b) gas licence applications made under the 33rd licensing roun", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oil and Natural Gas: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739350, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when his Department expects the North Sea Transition Authority to publish decisions on the remaining (a) oil and (b) gas licence applications made under the 33rd licensing round.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oil and Natural Gas: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739349, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many (a) oil and (b) gas licence applications made under the 33rd licensing round are yet to be determined.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oil and Natural Gas: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739348, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of the number of pending (a) oil and (b) gas licence applications delayed due to the judgement in UKSC 2022/0064.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oil and Natural Gas: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739347, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to incorporate the judgement in UKSC 2022/0064 into the decision-making process for oil and gas licences.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oil and Natural Gas: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739346, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many surrender bins there were during the knife amnesty between 26 August 2024 and 23 September 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739344, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much unusable PPE has been disposed of since November 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Protective Clothing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739343, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse is of storing PPE unsuitable for NHS use; and which companies are contracted to provide such storage services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Protective Clothing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739342, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on companies involved in supplying PPE which was subsequently marked as do not supply due to being unsuitable for use in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Protective Clothing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739339, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the guidance entitled Appointment of AUKUS Adviser and report: Terms of Reference, published on 29 August 2024, when he plans to publish Sir Stephen Lovegrove's report on AUKUS.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739338, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "12459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the guidance entitled Appointment of AUKUS Adviser and report: Terms of Reference, published on 29 August 2024, whether Sir Stephen Lovegrove reported his findings on AUKUS before the end of Oct", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739331, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the UK's obligation under Article 1 of the Genocide Convention to prevent genocide in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Genocide Convention", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739327, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12457", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to business rates relief on grassroots music venues.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739326, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12456", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has set a target for the impact of the Office for Value for Money on Government expenditure in each of the next three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Value for Money", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739325, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12455", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the potential impact of the Office for Value for Money on Government expenditure in each of the next three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Value for Money", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739324, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12454", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in the Office for Value for Money have a salary over \u00a3100,000.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Value for Money: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739321, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12453", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of forecast revenue from changes to Agricultural Property Relief in each financial year from 2024-25 to 2029-30.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739320, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to provide additional funding to local authorities for the cost of increases to employer National Insurance contributions.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739319, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12451", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, whether the Departmental settlements include funding for public sector employers for the cost of increases to employer National Insuran", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739303, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12450", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what steps she is taking to help increase prosecution rates for rural crime.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739302, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to implement a mechanism to ensure that intelligence information shared with the Israeli government is used within the boundaries of international humanitarian law, and what di", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739301, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to tackle homelessness among veteran communities in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739300, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has established a process for the (a) assessment and (b) retention of evidence gathered by unarmed RAF surveillance flights over Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739298, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on ensuring that any information gathered by unarmed RAF surveillance flights over Gaza can be used solely in relation to locating Israeli hostages.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739287, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 10 September 2024 to Questions 3805 and 3806 on Electric Vehicles: Charging Points, if she will hold discussions with (a) public and (b) private bodies on taking steps to ensure that ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739260, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to align the (a) scope and (b) implementation of the UK Deforestation Regulation (UKDR) with the European Union Deforestation Regulation; and when he plans to publish ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Forests: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739259, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the delay to the implementation of the European Union Deforestation Regulation; and what his planned timet", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Forests: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739258, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to promote UK-based food businesses to international markets.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Overseas Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739257, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to widen the scope for exporters to (a) licence and (b) use Government-generated brand identities for food and drink products.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Exports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739256, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,\u00a0whether his Department is taking steps with the food and drink industry to help tackle (a) poor diets and (b) obesity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nutrition: Obesity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739255, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of the extended producer responsibility scheme on (a) creating a circular economy for recycled materials and (b) ensuring bus", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Packaging: Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739254, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of introducing the proposed extended producer responsibility scheme on the cost to consumers of (a) essential foo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Packaging: Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739250, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a 10-year national cancer plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739249, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will help ensure that smoking cessation is offered as an opt-out, co-located service for lung screening appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Smoking: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739248, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to (a) maintain and (b) increase funding for local authority smoking cessation services; and if he will take steps to raise public awareness of those services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739228, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential health benefits of magnesium supplements.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Magnesium: Dietary Supplements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739217, "askingMemberId": 4753, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that new investment in further education contributes to (a) improving staff conditions and (b) closing pay gaps between college and school teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739216, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people released under the End of Custody Supervised Licence scheme have been (a) recalled, (b) released homeless, (c) died under supervision and (d) committed a serious further offence (i) since the sche", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739215, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department is taking steps with private mobile network operators to improve (a) mobile phone signal and (b) 5G coverage in London.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739214, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were released and later recalled to prison under the (a) End of Custody Supervised Licence, (b) Home Detention Curfew , and (c) SDS40 scheme (i) since the scheme was implemented and (ii) in the mo", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739196, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prevent the spread of Mpox.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mpox: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739195, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical technologies were (a) piloted in the NHS in (i) 2023 and (ii) 2024, (b) supported after successful pilots in those years and (c) adopted at scale in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Equipment: Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739194, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to reform colonoscopy services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Colonoscopy: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739193, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent to (a) outsource and (b) insource additional resource to manage colonoscopy procedures in each of the last five years by trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Colonoscopy: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739192, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were on waiting lists for colonoscopies in each year between 2020 and 2024 by trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Colonoscopy: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739184, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure timely responses to Pension Credit applications.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739183, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of salmon stocks in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Salmon", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739182, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will provide additional funding for prostate cancer (a) care and (b) research.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739181, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his Northern Irish counterpart on funding for hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739179, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the progress of research on treatments for (a) Alzheimer's and (b) dementia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739178, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to meet the target for 85% of cancer patients to be treated within 62 days of referral.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739177, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timeline is for the increase in the number of attendance mentors for schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739366, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12417", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to Recommendation 3 of the report entitled An inspection into activism and impartiality in policing, published by His Majesty\u2019s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services on 10 Se", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Public Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739364, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12415", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Cabinet Office\u2019s Government Procurement Card spend over \u00a3500 - July 2024, what the purpose was of the payments to (a) the Cookie Jar on 8 July 2024 and (b) Borgo Egnazia 6 on 17 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Electronic Purchasing Card Solution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739363, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12414", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster's letter to the Senior Salaries Review Body of 30 September 2024, whether public sector pay rises will be linked to productivity improvements in financial y", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739360, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12413", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Civil Service Fast Stream Recruitment Data 2024 published on 27 September 2024, for what reason the diversity data is collected by gender rather than sex.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739357, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) Kuwait, (b) Qatar and (c) Bahrain on their obligations under the International Covenant on Civil and Politi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739355, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what reforms she is considering to the eligibility rules for free school transport.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739337, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12409", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.51 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of changes to Agricultural Property Relief on family farms.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739335, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12408", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has had discussions with the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Select Committee on the potential impact of changes to Agricultural Property Relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739334, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12407", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings Ministers in her Department have had with farming stakeholders on changes to Agricultural Property Relief in the last four months.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739333, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12406", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what estimate her Department has made of the number of farms that will no longer be eligible for agricultural property relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739318, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to improve the communication of the real-time availability of ADHD medications in pharmacies to patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739317, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what support his Department provides for (a) wind and (b) solar power in the Overseas Territories.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power and Wind Power: British Overseas Territories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739316, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many cases of gun crime were reported in the Turks and Caicos Islands in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Turks and Caicos Islands: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739315, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many citizens of (a) Haiti and (b) the Dominican Republic are resident in Turks and Caicos.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Turks and Caicos Islands: Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739313, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of levels of crime in the Turks and Caicos islands.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Turks and Caicos Islands: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739312, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure a sustainable approach to fishing in the Overseas Territories.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Overseas Territories: Fisheries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739311, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that no fishing boats operate within the British Indian Ocean Territory Marine Protected Area.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Indian Ocean Territory: Fishing Vessels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739310, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has provided to neighbourhood watch organisations in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neighbourhood Watch Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739297, "askingMemberId": 4030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the contractual penalties are for the late transfer of prisoners to court; and at what point the penalty starts if a prisoner is transferred\u00a0late\u00a0to\u00a0court.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739296, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has had discussions with the National Energy System Operator on pylon presumption.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739293, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an estimate of the number of unfinanced energy projects in the queue to be connected to the power grid.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739290, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many fax machines are in use by the National Energy System Operator; and whether his Department plans to provide funding to digitalise the energy grid.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739289, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12393", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the potential impact of the costs of (a) VAT, (b) employers' National Insurance contributions, (c) employer contributions to the Teachers' Pension Scheme and (d) business rates for in", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: Employers' Contributions and VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739247, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with Motorway Service Area operators on the renewal of leases for those areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorway Service Areas: Leasehold", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739246, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to resolve the status of lease renewals of Motorway Service Areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorway Service Areas: Leasehold", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739245, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to extend the lease on the Motorway Service Area at Watford Gap.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorway Service Areas: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739227, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12389", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.51 of the Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what her Department's policy is on the application of inheritance tax to (a) unused pension funds and (b) death benef", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739190, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12387", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he the Government has plans to reduce the use of non-scheduled flights by Ministers.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Aviation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739180, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to encourage international investment across the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739358, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what extra funding he plans to provide for public health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739336, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he is taking steps to support Property Linked Finance to help homeowners to install (a) domestic renewables and (b) energy efficiency measures.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739332, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the (a) effectiveness of and (b) implications for his policies of recent investor-state dispute settlements under the bilateral investment treaty with Colombia; and whe", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treaties: Colombia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739309, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support existing neighbourhood watch organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neighbourhood Watch Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739208, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12380", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the joint sex and age-at-death distribution was for Covid-19 deaths in 2020 in England that were subject to inquest and have since been registered with ONS for which the interval from date of death to date ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Death: Coronavirus", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739207, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring all local authorities to provide drivers with the option of paying for parking by cash.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739206, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce delays to cladding remediation works.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "High Rise Flats: Fire Prevention", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739205, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce waiting times for practical driving tests in (a) Greater London and (b) Essex.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Essex and Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739204, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring cyclists to (a) display number plates and (b) hold valid insurance.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cycling: Insurance and Vehicle Number Plates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739203, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to encourage employers to hire people with disabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739202, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help repair potholes in Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Romford", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739201, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department have had with animal welfare charities to discuss (i) puppy and cat smuggling and (ii) a ban of electronic shock collars ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739200, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding he is providing for people with brain tumours in financial year 2024/25.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Tumours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739199, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the MHRA is considering the approval of vorasidenib for the treatment of low grade gliomas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vorasidenib", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739198, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of vorasdenib for treatment of low-grade gliomas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vorasidenib", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739341, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to ensure that elections are accessible to (a) blind and (b) partially sighted people.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Visual Impairment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739340, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers are employed in neighbourhood policing in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Policing: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739286, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing funding for the Spalding Flower Parade.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parades: Spalding", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739221, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support early speech and language interventions in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739220, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the waiting times for (a) assessments for and (b) diagnoses of\u00a0autism\u00a0in (i) adults and (ii) children in (A) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (B) Linco", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Autism: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739219, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set up a cross-departmental working group to discuss how to increase the fertility rate.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fertility", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739368, "askingMemberId": 249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12361", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to ensure that the rise in employer National Insurance contributions does not apply to general practices.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: General Practitioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739356, "askingMemberId": 249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12360", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to ensure that the rise in employer National Insurance contributions does not apply to hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Hospices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739292, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that a code is created for myalgic encephalomyelitis in the SNOMED CT classification system in primary care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chronic Fatigue Syndrome: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739218, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2024 to Question 10405 on Driving Licences: Foreign Nationals, if she will hold discussions with the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency on the potential merits of recording", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Licences: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739291, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how codes are created for the SNOMED CT classification system in primary care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Records: Classification Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1739354, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-06T00:00:00", "uin": "12356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to Huawei's press article entitled, Safe Mauritius, the Inspiration for Heaven, published in October 2018, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the s", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mauritius: Telecommunications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1739354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738759, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12355", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse is of the UK Commission on Covid Commemoration.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Commission on Covid Commemoration: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738758, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12354", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse is of the covid-19 inquiry; if he will make an estimate of the anticipated total cost of the inquiry; and whether the inquiry is running to budget.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Covid-19 Inquiry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738757, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to encourage Forestry England to introducing disabled parking spaces in the Bourne Woods car park, Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bourne Wood: Parking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738756, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking with (a) local authorities and (b) businesses to help reduce plastic waste.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plastics: Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738755, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle plastic pollution in (a) rural and (b) coastal areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plastics: Coastal Areas and Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738754, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department plans to provide to help manage the increased flood risk for rural areas prone to (a) river and (b) surface flooding in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738745, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle knife crime in late night venues.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738743, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will issue guidance to schools to make clear every child with epilepsy is entitled to have an Individual Healthcare Plan with (a) information about their epilepsy and (b) any support they need.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Epilepsy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738742, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many irregular migrants are in (a) social and (b) council housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Social Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738737, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with the devolved Administrations to help (a) reduce waiting times for gynaecological services and (b) address menstrual health inequalities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gynaecology: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738736, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12344", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made an assessment of introducing performance related pay reviews on all senior leadership positions in the Civil Service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Senior Civil Servants: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738735, "askingMemberId": 5229, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including publicly accessible trust data in the Register of Overseas Entities.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Companies: Property", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738732, "askingMemberId": 5307, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to take steps to introduce a national phase-out of the use of pesticides in public areas under local authority control.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pesticides: Public Places", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738730, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12340", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil service staff worked on Whitehall in (a) January 2024 and (b) the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Whitehall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738728, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 11148 on Local Plans, if she will write to leaders of local authorities to ask for Local Growth Plans.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Plans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738716, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "12337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing incentives on the use of heat batteries similar to those on heat pumps.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738706, "askingMemberId": 5229, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans he has to publish the results of the UK and Overseas Territories Joint Ministerial Council on 19-21 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Territories Joint Ministerial Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738705, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department taking steps to prevent (a) members of Tehreek-e-Labbaik Pakistan and (b) others involved in violent incidents against Ahmadi Muslims in Pakistan from entering the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration Controls: Pakistan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738704, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12332", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many days were lost to strike action in the Civil Service in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Strikes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738703, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12331", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what percentage of the food served at receptions in Number 10 Downing Street is domestically produced.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "10 Downing Street: Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738701, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to roll out NHS-funded Hybrid Close Loop technology to all Type 1 Diabetics in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Medical Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738696, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of the cost to the public purse of irregular migration in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738695, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were referred to the Prevent programme by their ideological motivation in each year since 2014.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radicalism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738694, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse was of storing personal protective equipment in China since the outbreak of the covid-19 pandemic.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Protective Clothing: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738693, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much and what proportion of personal protective equipment (PPE) purchased to respond to covid-19 was incinerated; and what the value was of the incinerated PPE.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Protective Clothing: Coronavirus", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738692, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of seeking reparations from China for their alleged role in the (a) production and (b) release of covid-19.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Coronavirus", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738688, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12323", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes to agricultural property relief and business property relief", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738687, "askingMemberId": 5267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12322", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many estates in Earley and Woodley constituency were subject to inheritance tax in\u00a0tax years (a) 2019/20, (b) 2020/21 and (c) 2021/22.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inheritance Tax: Earley and Woodley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738686, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding her Department plans to provide through the UK Shared Prosperity Fund to projects in Northern Ireland in the 2024-25 financial year; and if she will take steps t", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Shared Prosperity Fund: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738679, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2024 to Question 11104 on Terrorism, if she will publish a breakdown of the ideological motivations for the 43 late-stage attack plots disrupted since March 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Terrorism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738674, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to increase awareness amongst GPs of the signs and symptoms of cardiomyopathy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738671, "askingMemberId": 5360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the accessibility of Cantonese-language guidance to Hongkongers applying for eVisa to replace their Biometric Residence Permit.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738656, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of maintenance loans for students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738655, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new prison places are scheduled to be built in the next 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738654, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to improve mental health provision for farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Farmers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738653, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.70 of Autumn Budget 2024, HC 295, published on 30 October 2024, what estimate he has made of the proportion of additional funding for the NHS that will be spent on (a)", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738652, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12310", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to reduce import duties on businesses spending less than \u00a310,000 on goods in Europe on a single trip.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Import Duties: UK Trade with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738651, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12309", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to reduce the administrative requirements for businesses spending less than \u00a310,000 on a single trip in Europe.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Trade with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738650, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will hold discussions with freight companies on the cost of transporting small vans across the Channel.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Freight: Channel Tunnel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738649, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12307", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to simplify the (a) commodity code system, (b) requirements to weigh items and (c) other administrative requirements for businesses operating cross-border trade.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738752, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will make it his policy to require (a) unused and (b) decommissioned (i) laptops, (ii) mobile phones and (iii) other public sector devices to be donated to device banks.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Public Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738751, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring the Jobcentre Plus to signpost people to digital inclusion services.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jobcentres: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738750, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of (a) recruitment and (b) retention in police forces.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Labour Turnover and Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738748, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what percentage of police officers are currently classified as deployable; and what the primary reasons are for officers being deemed non-deployable.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Deployment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738744, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has allocated funding towards the future of Cheadle Train Station.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Cheadle", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738740, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "12300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) any Ministers from his Department held meetings with Representative Vincent Yao from the Taipei Representative Office in the UK in (i) September and (i", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738739, "askingMemberId": 4603, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of workers that will benefit from the increase to the (a) National Minimum Wage and (b) National Living Wage in Birmingham.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Living Wage and Minimum Wage: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738738, "askingMemberId": 4603, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many workers aged above 16 years old are paid within 50p of the (a) National Minimum Wage and (b) National Living Wage in (i) Birmingham and (ii) the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Living Wage and Minimum Wage: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738727, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to extend the statutory override on the treatment of deficits to the dedicated schools grant after the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dedicated Schools Grant", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738698, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of childcare places in rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738691, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.19 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, when she plans to publish further information on her plan to increase capacity on the West Coast main line.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "West Coast Main Line", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738690, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12288", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.30 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, when she plans to publish a consultation on the proposed Infrastructure Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738684, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "12286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average processing time is for a new claim for Pension Credit from initial application to determination.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738663, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.19 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, when she plans to publish further information on her plan to increase capacity on the West Coast main line.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "West Coast Main Line", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738662, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.72 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, whether she plans to publish a consultation on the proposed rolling stock strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rolling Stock", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738661, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12277", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she plans to publish the timetable for the consultation on the proposed infrastructure strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738660, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.16 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, where the proposed locations are of the three large housing development sites in", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738657, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12275", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister\u2019s speech of 6 July 2024 and to the Cabinet Office guidance entitled List of Cabinet Committees and their membership, updated on 21 October 2024, for what reason the Prime Min", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738749, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether goals to improve (a) access to and (b) engagement with nature are part of the Rapid Review of the current Environmental Improvement Plan; and what plans he has to engage with s", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738747, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department will continue to support the continuation of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme which is due to expire\u00a0in\u00a0March\u00a02025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738726, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the number of Education and Health Care Plans that will be issued for qualifying young people (a) nationwide and (b) in Essex in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738725, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, how much SEND funding she plans to allocate to local authorities to (a) cover existing DSG deficits and (b) for future spending pr", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738724, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding will be allocated to support pupils with SEND in Essex in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Essex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738721, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12267", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the OECD Pillar 2 measures on businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Corporation Tax: International Cooperation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738720, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12266", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the revenue raised as a result of the OECD Pillar 2 measures in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Corporation Tax: International Cooperation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738719, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12265", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse through (a) third party spend and (b) contracts as a result of changes to em", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Government Departments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738718, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12264", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, what the Resource DEL provided to each Department in respect of the impact of the changes to employers National Insurance Contributions", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Government Departments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738717, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12263", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to line 26 of Table 5.1 of the Autumn Budget 2024, published on 30 October 2024, HC 295, which public sector organisations will be funded to cover the additional costs of the changes to employers Nati", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Public Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738682, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Network Rail\u2019s targets to improve railway adhesion in Control Period 7 between 2024 and 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738672, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12260", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 14 May 2024 on Equality, Diversity and Inclusion in the Civil Service, HCWS464, and pursuant to the Answers of 19 September 2024 to Question 5049 and of 16 September 20", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738659, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12259", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of issuing guidance on (a) accepting and (b) declaring (i) donations in kind, (ii) gifts and (iii) sponsorship of retail goods or services by commercial orga", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Gifts and Endowments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738681, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Network Rail\u2019s management of railway adhesion in Control Period 6 between 2019 and 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738746, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12250", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the number of farmers who will be affected by the withdrawal of agricultural property relief in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738678, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12249", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will list which external organisations her Department consulted before the change in policy on inheritance tax for agricultural properties.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738677, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has provided funding to Hope Not Hate since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HOPE not hate: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738676, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what external bodies her Department consulted before calculating revised\u00a0housing targets.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1738675, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2024-11-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2024-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "12245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect the coastline of the Wash from erosion.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coastal Erosion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1738675", "method": "GET"}]}]